<news>
	<post>
		<id>2709</id>
		<title>
			<span style="color: red">Maintenance Window</span>
		</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>During winter break, the Systems Administrators will be performing maintenance on a number of important systems including Iodine, the TJ Webserver, and the TJ Remote Access Server. We will post specific downtime notices here as we schedule maintenance, however, please keep in mind that many systems will need to be taken down at least briefly for maintenance.</p><p>If you have any questions, please email <a href="mailto:sysadmins@lists.tjhsst.edu">sysadmins@lists.tjhsst.edu</a> or <a href="mailto:ahamilto@tjhsst.edu">ahamilto@tjhsst.edu</a>.</p><p>Thank you in advance for your patience and enjoy your break!</p><p>Andrew Hamilton<br />Network / Systems Elf</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
During winter break, the Systems Administrators will be performing maintenance on a number of important systems including Iodine, the TJ Webserver, and the TJ Remote Access Server. We will post specific downtime notices here as we schedule maintenance, however, please keep in mind that many systems will need to be taken down at least briefly for maintenance. If you have any questions, please email sysadmins@lists.tjhsst.edu or ahamilto@tjhsst.edu. Thank you in advance for your patience and enjoy your break! Andrew HamiltonNetwork / Systems Elf
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2706</id>
		<title>Please submit your non-sensitive Science Fair forms</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
Attention TJ Science Fair participants: Please submit your nonsensitive science fair project forms to room 141 work by Friday, January 9. Remember, this is the first week after the winter break!<div><br /></div><div>Also a reminder for sensitive projects: Your paperwork has been reviewed by TJ's Scientific Review Committee. Please find your sponsor ASAP for a list of necessary corrections, and see Dr. Burden in 141wk before winter break to discuss how to correct your submission.</div><div><br /></div><div>For any other questions or concerns, please email Dr. Burden (<a href="mailto:dkburden@fcps.edu">dkburden@fcps.edu</a>), or visit his office in room 141 wk. </div>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Attention TJ Science Fair participants: Please submit your nonsensitive science fair project forms to room 141 work by Friday, January 9. Remember, this is the first week after the winter break!Also a reminder for sensitive projects: Your paperwork has been reviewed by TJ's Scientific Review Committee. Please find your sponsor ASAP for a list of necessary corrections, and see Dr. Burden in 141wk before winter break to discuss how to correct your submission.For any other questions or concerns, please email Dr. Burden (dkburden@fcps.edu), or visit his office in room 141 wk.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>1876</id>
		<title>STEMbassador volunteer opportunities</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom:.0001pt;line-height:normal;"><span style="font-size:10pt;">Volunteer opportunities in Fairfax and Arlington County (other opportunities to be posted soon). Become a STEMbassador and give back to your local elementary and middle schools through tutoring and mentoring kids on weekends, evenings, 8th period, or during the summer. <br /></span><span style="font-family:Calibri, sans-serif;font-size:11pt;line-height:115%;"></span><span style="font-family:Calibri, sans-serif;font-size:11pt;line-height:15.3333320617676px;"></span></p><ul><li><span style="font-family:Calibri, sans-serif;font-size:15px;line-height:15.3333320617676px;">Herndon Middle School (Herndon): Coach needed for VEX IQ robotics on Tues (5-7pm) and/or Wed (6:00-7:30) evenings until the January 31 competition.  Location is the </span><span style="font-family:Calibri, sans-serif;font-size:15px;line-height:15.3333320617676px;">Herndon Neighborhood Resource Center  in the Dulles Park Shopping Center.</span></li><li><span style="font-family:Calibri, sans-serif;font-size:15px;line-height:15.3333320617676px;">Mount Eagle Elementary School (Alexandria): Volunteers needed to run stations on STEM night, January 15, from 6:30-8:30pm. </span></li><li><span style="line-height:115%;">Frost Middle School (Fairfax): Need virtual/internet mentors to teach entomology to the Science Olympiad time.  Times vary based on availability.</span></li><li><span style="line-height:115%;">Lincolnia Community Resource Center (Alexandria):  Tutors needed on any weekdays from 4:00pm-6:30pm or Saturdays from 10am-12pm.</span></li><li><span style="line-height:15.3333320617676px;">Whitefield Community Resource Center (Arlington):  Tutors needed on any weekdays from 4:00pm-6:30pm or Saturdays from 10am-12pm.</span></li><li>Washington International Academy (Alexandria): Tutors for grades 4-7 needed from 3:30-5:30pm Monday through Thursday (where possible)</li><li><a href="http://www.tjhsst.edu/~emglazer/Childrens%20Science%20Center%20Mobile%20Labs%20Family%20Science%20Nights%202014-2015%20advertisement.pdf" style="font-size:10pt;line-height:115%;text-indent:-.25in;">Mini Lab events for the 2014-2015 school year</a><span style="line-height:115%;text-indent:-.25in;">: </span><span style="font-size:13px;font-family:Arial, sans-serif;line-height:115%;text-indent:-.25in;">These Children Science Center sessions seek volunteers for four hour sessions at elementary schools.  Volunteers must be at least 16 years old.</span><br /></li></ul><span style="line-height:115%;">Email </span><a href="mailto:stembassadors@tjhsst.edu" style="font-size:10pt;line-height:115%;">stembassadors@tjhsst.edu</a><span style="line-height:115%;"> if you would like to participate in one of these service activities.  </span><a href="http://www.tjhsst.edu/~emglazer/STEMbassadors.php" style="font-size:10pt;line-height:115%;">More info about STEMbassadors</a><br /><p class="MsoNormal"><span style="font-size:10pt;line-height:115%;"></span></p><a href="http://www.tjhsst.edu/~emglazer/STEMbassadors.php"></a>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Volunteer opportunities in Fairfax and Arlington County (other opportunities to be posted soon). Become a STEMbassador and give back to your local elementary and middle schools through tutoring and mentoring kids on weekends, evenings, 8th period, or during the summer.   Herndon Middle School (Herndon): Coach needed for VEX IQ robotics on Tues (5-7pm) and/or Wed (6:00-7:30) evenings until the January 31 competition.  Location is the Herndon Neighborhood Resource Center  in the Dulles Park Shopping Center.Mount Eagle Elementary School (Alexandria): Volunteers needed to run stations on STEM night, January 15, from 6:30-8:30pm. Frost Middle School (Fairfax): Need virtual/internet mentors to teach entomology to the Science Olympiad time.  Times vary based on availability.Lincolnia Community Resource Center (Alexandria):  Tutors needed on any weekdays from 4:00pm-6:30pm or Saturdays from 10am-12pm.Whitefield Community Resource Center (Arlington):  Tutors needed on any weekdays from 4:00pm-6:30pm or Saturdays from 10am-12pm.Washington International Academy (Alexandria): Tutors for grades 4-7 needed from 3:30-5:30pm Monday through Thursday (where possible)Mini Lab events for the 2014-2015 school year: These Children Science Center sessions seek volunteers for four hour sessions at elementary schools.  Volunteers must be at least 16 years old.Email stembassadors@tjhsst.edu if you would like to participate in one of these service activities.  More info about STEMbassadors
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2697</id>
		<title>FCPSonboard - more info</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Most of the privacy concerns regarding FCPSonboard are related to the XpressConnect app. Here&#8217;s a few things you may want to know about this app:</p><ul><li>The app is used to download a certificate that authenticates your FCPS credentials and puts you on the correct wireless network. <b>Once you&#8217;ve installed the certificate, you no longer need the app and you can and delete it.</b></li><li>You have to reset your FCPS password every school year (this also resets your FCPS GAE password). You also have to renew the certificate every school year with your new credentials. Thus, after you reset your FCPS password each school year, you will also need to re-join FCPSonboard and re-download the XpressConnect app to reinstall the certificate. So you only need to have the app on your phone for a few minutes once every school year. Once the certificate is installed, you can delete XpressConnect.</li><li>This app is not downloaded on iOS devices-they have a different method of installing the certificate</li></ul><p>If you need help connecting your device to the WiFi, please see Ms. Tecuci in room 14.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Most of the privacy concerns regarding FCPSonboard are related to the XpressConnect app. Here&#8217;s a few things you may want to know about this app: The app is used to download a certificate that authenticates your FCPS credentials and puts you on the correct wireless network. Once you&#8217;ve installed the certificate, you no longer need the app and you can and delete it. You have to reset your FCPS password every school year (this also resets your FCPS GAE password). You also have to renew the certificate every school year with your new credentials. Thus, after you reset your FCPS password each school year, you will also need to re-join FCPSonboard and re-download the XpressConnect app to reinstall the certificate. So you only need to have the app on your phone for a few minutes once every school year. Once the certificate is installed, you can delete XpressConnect. This app is not downloaded on iOS devices-they have a different method of installing the certificate If you need help connecting your device to the WiFi, please see Ms. Tecuci in room 14.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2692</id>
		<title>TJ Band Concerts on December 12/15</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Come see the TJ Bands at our Winter Concert Friday December 12 A &amp; B block and Monday December 15 B block. The Symphonic Band (A Block) and the Wind Ensemble (B Block) play the 12th. The Jazz Ensemble and Combo play the 15th.</p><p>Featuring selections such as:</p><ul><li>Family Guy Theme</li><li>Monsters Inc. Theme</li><li>Sleigh Ride</li><li>Deck the Halls</li><li>Pirates of the Caribbean</li><li>The Nightmare Before Christmas</li><li>Howl's Moving Castle</li><li>Lord of the Rings</li></ul><p>It's gonna be a great concert and we hope to see you there!</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Come see the TJ Bands at our Winter Concert Friday December 12 A &amp; B block and Monday December 15 B block. The Symphonic Band (A Block) and the Wind Ensemble (B Block) play the 12th. The Jazz Ensemble and Combo play the 15th. Featuring selections such as: Family Guy Theme Monsters Inc. Theme Sleigh Ride Deck the Halls Pirates of the Caribbean The Nightmare Before Christmas Howl's Moving Castle Lord of the Rings It's gonna be a great concert and we hope to see you there!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2691</id>
		<title>Reporting Service Learning Hours</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Our school is now using a pilot program called x2VOL to track student service learning hours. This program will allow you to log your service hours online through Blackboard and Family Connection. X2VOL will enable you to keep track of your activities and hours as you perform them. You will need to sign on to Blackboard/Family Connection to create a profile and then you will be able to enter all your service learning activities as you go along and the program will total your hours for each year and provide a cumulative report at the end of your senior year. If you complete at least 40 hours by the time you graduate, you will receive a black cord to wear with your cap and gown. These two links provide instructions to set up your account and an overview of the program. If you have any questions, please contact Cathie Love at <a href="mailto:cmlove@fcps.edu">cmlove@fcps.edu</a>.</p><p>See <a href="https://www.tjhsst.edu/~2016jwoglom/uploads/x2VOL%20Guide%20for%20TJHSST%20Students.docx">the student guide</a> and <a href="https://www.tjhsst.edu/~2016jwoglom/uploads/x2VOL%20Student%20Login%20for%20TJHSST%20Expanded%20Version.ppt"> presentation</a>.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Our school is now using a pilot program called x2VOL to track student service learning hours. This program will allow you to log your service hours online through Blackboard and Family Connection. X2VOL will enable you to keep track of your activities and hours as you perform them. You will need to sign on to Blackboard/Family Connection to create a profile and then you will be able to enter all your service learning activities as you go along and the program will total your hours for each year and provide a cumulative report at the end of your senior year. If you complete at least 40 hours by the time you graduate, you will receive a black cord to wear with your cap and gown. These two links provide instructions to set up your account and an overview of the program. If you have any questions, please contact Cathie Love at cmlove@fcps.edu. See the student guide and presentation.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2690</id>
		<title>Printing Disruptions Possible in the Library</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Due to renovation-related demolition, library computer and printing services may be disrupted. Please plan on printing from home.</p><p>--The Librarians</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Due to renovation-related demolition, library computer and printing services may be disrupted. Please plan on printing from home.--The Librarians
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2687</id>
		<title>One Question Activity Monday</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p class="MsoNormal">No Monday 8th period plans?</p><p class="MsoNormal">The One Question steering committee will be hosting a special, winter-themed 8th period event on Monday, December 8th. There will be stations to decorate cookies and make t-shirts.There will also be a painting competition, and winners will win gift cards to Starbucks! </p><p class="MsoNormal">So, sign up and come with your friends to relax, have fun, and pursue your passions!<br /></p><p class="MsoNormal"></p><p></p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
No Monday 8th period plans?The One Question steering committee will be hosting a special, winter-themed 8th period event on Monday, December 8th. There will be stations to decorate cookies and make t-shirts.There will also be a painting competition, and winners will win gift cards to Starbucks! So, sign up and come with your friends to relax, have fun, and pursue your passions!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2686</id>
		<title>Winter Sports!</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>All student tickets for home regular season games and/or meets for the winter season have been paid for by tjSGA! Show your student ID or Intranet account at the door for free admission. Come out and support your athletic teams! </p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
All student tickets for home regular season games and/or meets for the winter season have been paid for by tjSGA! Show your student ID or Intranet account at the door for free admission. Come out and support your athletic teams!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2683</id>
		<title>
8th Pd Detention is NEXT WEEK - clear your absences NOW
</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<span style="font-size:15px;">The list for 8th period detention is being created this week! PLEASE CLEAR YOUR ABSENCES. </span><span style="font-size:15px;">To be removed you must clear your 8th period absences BEFORE 4pm on Tuesday, December 9. </span><span style="font-size:15px;">Many from Novembe
]]>
			<![CDATA[
r may still be cleared. How?</span><p> It's simple: click on the absence link from your home page, print the page and ask the teacher to sign off that you were there -- be sure to include your name, your ID, the name of the activity that you attended. Return the sheet to room 231 and you're done! </p><p> To keep from getting an absence:<b><br /></b></p><ul><li><b>Go to the activity that you chose -- and don't leave!</b></li><li>Make sure your teacher knows you are there.</li><li>DO NOT sign the bottom of a roster or attendance sheet. These names are not included in attendance and will result in an absence. </li><li><b>Don't ask a <u>substitute</u> to 'call you in', they can't! Absences in activities with a substitute teacher cannot be cleared!</b><br /></li><li>Turn in your pass to the sponsor as soon as you arrive! </li><li>QUESTIONS? See Mrs. Burch or Mrs. Lauducci in the 8th period office (room 231)</li></ul>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
The list for 8th period detention is being created this week! PLEASE CLEAR YOUR ABSENCES. To be removed you must clear your 8th period absences BEFORE 4pm on Tuesday, December 9. Many from November may still be cleared. How? It's simple: click on the absence link from your home page, print the page and ask the teacher to sign off that you were there -- be sure to include your name, your ID, the name of the activity that you attended. Return the sheet to room 231 and you're done! To keep from getting an absence:Go to the activity that you chose -- and don't leave!Make sure your teacher knows you are there.DO NOT sign the bottom of a roster or attendance sheet. These names are not included in attendance and will result in an absence. Don't ask a substitute to 'call you in', they can't! Absences in activities with a substitute teacher cannot be cleared!Turn in your pass to the sponsor as soon as you arrive! QUESTIONS? See Mrs. Burch or Mrs. Lauducci in the 8th period office (room 231)
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2681</id>
		<title>FCPSOnBoard - Starts Tomorrow</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p class="MsoNormal">Starting on Thursday, Dec. 4, if you want to use the school WiFi, you will need to select FCPSonboard and <u>carefully follow the directions to join the network</u>.  You must have your FCPS password activated this year (this was done if you activated your FCPS Google Apps account this year), or alternatively use the guest account.  If you do not know your FCPS password or need to reset it, you may ask any teacher for assistance.</p><p></p><p class="MsoNormal"></p><p></p><p class="MsoNormal">If you need assistance joining the FCPSonboard network, please see the links below for specific instructions for your operating system.</p><p></p><p class="MsoNormal"></p><p><a href="http://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;rct=j&amp;q=fcpsonboard&amp;source=web&amp;cd=1&amp;cad=rja&amp;uact=8&amp;ved=0CCAQFjAA&amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.fcps.edu%2FHayfieldES%2Fdocs%2Fbyod%2FFCPS%2520Onboard%2520Android%2520Devices.pdf&amp;ei=xnN_VOCVFcWcgwTW3YG4Dg&amp;usg=AFQjCNG5Ep5YJRezqhd9SSey8DT_I8rDdg&amp;sig2=mRzNWV2Jap15mq7TO1o3AA&amp;bvm=bv.80642063,d.eXY">Android</a> Instructions</p><p class="MsoNormal"></p><p><a href="http://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;rct=j&amp;q=fcpsonboard&amp;source=web&amp;cd=2&amp;cad=rja&amp;uact=8&amp;ved=0CCYQFjAB&amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.fcps.edu%2FStoneMS%2FTechnology%2Ffcps-onboard-windows-wireless-configuration.pdf&amp;ei=xnN_VOCVFcWcgwTW3YG4Dg&amp;usg=AFQjCNGrED7RqqxfvWeRvmMSkpRDHfpsag&amp;sig2=b7trY_nzP7HGCpuUUU43Aw&amp;bvm=bv.80642063,d.eXY">Windows OS</a> Instructions</p><p class="MsoNormal"></p><p><a href="http://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;rct=j&amp;q=fcpsonboard&amp;source=web&amp;cd=3&amp;cad=rja&amp;uact=8&amp;ved=0CCwQFjAC&amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.fcps.edu%2FStoneMS%2FTechnology%2Ffcps-onboard-apple-wireless-configuration.pdf&amp;ei=xnN_VOCVFcWcgwTW3YG4Dg&amp;usg=AFQjCNEpabAj0mpYteQHJG9txsoSigMYNQ&amp;sig2=5GHYke0SoQ3xVJRkK9Ebxg&amp;bvm=bv.80642063,d.eXY">Apple OS </a>Instructions</p><p class="MsoNormal">Additional assistance will be provided by the Computer Tech Assistants club in the Aud Lob on Friday during 8<sup>th</sup> period A block, as well as on Monday during 8<sup>th</sup> period.</p><p></p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Starting on Thursday, Dec. 4, if you want to use the school WiFi, you will need to select FCPSonboard and carefully follow the directions to join the network.  You must have your FCPS password activated this year (this was done if you activated your FCPS Google Apps account this year), or alternatively use the guest account.  If you do not know your FCPS password or need to reset it, you may ask any teacher for assistance.   If you need assistance joining the FCPSonboard network, please see the links below for specific instructions for your operating system. Android InstructionsWindows OS InstructionsApple OS Instructions Additional assistance will be provided by the Computer Tech Assistants club in the Aud Lob on Friday during 8th period A block, as well as on Monday during 8th period.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2677</id>
		<title>Seniors -- Apply to MC iNite 2015!</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Do you think you're funny? Do you think you'd look good on stage? Are you dependent on breathing Oxygen? Do you want to MC the largest high school event in the Washington Metro Area? <a href="http://goo.gl/forms/Ppm7oUpd99">Sign up here!</a></p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Do you think you're funny? Do you think you'd look good on stage? Are you dependent on breathing Oxygen? Do you want to MC the largest high school event in the Washington Metro Area? Sign up here!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2672</id>
		<title>Poetry Out Loud</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
It is that time of year again! Time for TJ&#8217;s 7th Annual Poetry Out Loud Recitation Contest. The first grade-level competition will be on Wednesday, November 19th during both A and B blocks in the auditorium. If you need additional information, please contact Mrs. Henry at <a href="mailto:shenry@fcps.edu">shenry@fcps.edu</a>. Come out and support the spoken word!
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
It is that time of year again! Time for TJ&#8217;s 7th Annual Poetry Out Loud Recitation Contest. The first grade-level competition will be on Wednesday, November 19th during both A and B blocks in the auditorium. If you need additional information, please contact Mrs. Henry at shenry@fcps.edu. Come out and support the spoken word!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2671</id>
		<title>
You have NOT properly set up your Google Apps account
</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Oh my gosh, Juniors and Seniors who STILL do not have GAE (Google Apps, @fcpsschools.net) accounts should sign up for the upcoming available sessions during 8th period, starting Nov. 12 and Nov. 19. <b style="font-size:16px;color:#FF0000;">If you are seeing this message, you have NOT properly set up your Google Apps account.</b> Alternatively, come on a Monday or Wednesday to either side of the library at the beginning of lunch, only. You need passwords for these accounts for several reasons: items that affect your grades are being collected using the GAE accounts. Signing up for a senior lab requires a GAE account, juniors, and that process begins real soon! The FCPS password is needed to get onto FCPSmobile network. THAT is the only network you can use to access by proxy to library databases when you are using a personal device on campus. The other school networks don&#8217;t give data base access by proxy on campus. We&#8217;ll explain all of this in the session. You&#8217;ll have extra time when we&#8217;re done with the account set ups to treat as a study hall. See you then if you are STILL not accessing your GAE account. We want to help! </p><p><br /></p><p>--Mrs. Carpenter</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Oh my gosh, Juniors and Seniors who STILL do not have GAE (Google Apps, @fcpsschools.net) accounts should sign up for the upcoming available sessions during 8th period, starting Nov. 12 and Nov. 19. If you are seeing this message, you have NOT properly set up your Google Apps account. Alternatively, come on a Monday or Wednesday to either side of the library at the beginning of lunch, only. You need passwords for these accounts for several reasons: items that affect your grades are being collected using the GAE accounts. Signing up for a senior lab requires a GAE account, juniors, and that process begins real soon! The FCPS password is needed to get onto FCPSmobile network. THAT is the only network you can use to access by proxy to library databases when you are using a personal device on campus. The other school networks don&#8217;t give data base access by proxy on campus. We&#8217;ll explain all of this in the session. You&#8217;ll have extra time when we&#8217;re done with the account set ups to treat as a study hall. See you then if you are STILL not accessing your GAE account. We want to help! --Mrs. Carpenter
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2667</id>
		<title>Computational Linguistic Olympiad</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Interested in computer science? World languages? Puzzles? If so, then the NACLO competition may just be for you. The North American Computational Linguistic Olympiad is a contest in which high-school students solve linguistic puzzles. In solving these puzzles, students learn about the diversity and consistency of language, while exercising logic skills. No prior knowledge of linguistics or second languages is necessary. Professionals in linguistics, computational linguistics and language technologies use dozens of languages to create engaging problems that represent cutting edge issues in their fields. The competition has attracted top students to study and work in those same fields. It is truly an opportunity for young people to experience a taste of natural-language processing in the 21st century. The first round contest will take place on January 29. Practices will be held on Fridays starting this week during B-block in T19. Sign up for NACLO practice to see what the fun is all about! (You can still participate if you can&#8217;t come to the practices, <a href="mailto:rgalanos@fcps.edu">email Miss Galanos (rgalanos@fcps.edu)</a> for details.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Interested in computer science? World languages? Puzzles? If so, then the NACLO competition may just be for you. The North American Computational Linguistic Olympiad is a contest in which high-school students solve linguistic puzzles. In solving these puzzles, students learn about the diversity and consistency of language, while exercising logic skills. No prior knowledge of linguistics or second languages is necessary. Professionals in linguistics, computational linguistics and language technologies use dozens of languages to create engaging problems that represent cutting edge issues in their fields. The competition has attracted top students to study and work in those same fields. It is truly an opportunity for young people to experience a taste of natural-language processing in the 21st century. The first round contest will take place on January 29. Practices will be held on Fridays starting this week during B-block in T19. Sign up for NACLO practice to see what the fun is all about! (You can still participate if you can&#8217;t come to the practices, email Miss Galanos (rgalanos@fcps.edu) for details.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2666</id>
		<title>TJ Email Forwarding</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>TJ uses your Webmail address for communications. That&#8217;s your @tjhsst.edu address that you access with your local domain ID and password. It&#8217;s linked from Iodine&#8217;s login screen. If you need assistance to forward your @tjhsst.edu email to a preferred address, use this help:</p><a href="https://livedoc.tjhsst.edu/wiki/Forwarding_your_TJ_Email">https://livedoc.tjhsst.edu/wiki/Forwarding_your_TJ_Email</a><p> For help about your @tjhsst.edu webmail, contact mailadmins@tjhsst.edu.</p><p> ALSO, did you know that Blackboard needs you to have a CURRENT email address listed under &#8220;TOOLS: Personal Information&#8221; on the home screen? If you don&#8217;t have an updated email address there, you are probably missing out on vital communications&#8212;especially if you are a sophomore, junior or senior. </p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
TJ uses your Webmail address for communications. That&#8217;s your @tjhsst.edu address that you access with your local domain ID and password. It&#8217;s linked from Iodine&#8217;s login screen. If you need assistance to forward your @tjhsst.edu email to a preferred address, use this help: https://livedoc.tjhsst.edu/wiki/Forwarding_your_TJ_Email For help about your @tjhsst.edu webmail, contact mailadmins@tjhsst.edu. ALSO, did you know that Blackboard needs you to have a CURRENT email address listed under &#8220;TOOLS: Personal Information&#8221; on the home screen? If you don&#8217;t have an updated email address there, you are probably missing out on vital communications&#8212;especially if you are a sophomore, junior or senior.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2663</id>
		<title>
TJTED: Interview Foreign Ambassadors - country assignment this Friday
</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>TJTED is having a meeting this Friday B Block for the Ambassador Project, a project in which students will <b>contact and interview foreign ambassadors</b> to gain a better understanding of diplomacy and international relations. This Friday's meeting will serve to compile contact information of foreign ambassadors to the US, and to start assigning countries to pairs of students.</p><p>Because the interviews will take place in pairs, we strongly encourage that both you and your partner attend Friday&#8217;s meeting. The groups that help to compile the contact information on Friday will have the <b>first pick of the country</b> whose ambassador they will contact and interview. Preliminary research of your choices of consideration is strongly suggested.</p><p>Email TJTED at <a href="mailto:tjtechnocrats@gmail.com">tjtechnocrats@gmail.com</a> to get the project description handout, if you missed the interest meeting, or if you have any questions.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
TJTED is having a meeting this Friday B Block for the Ambassador Project, a project in which students will contact and interview foreign ambassadors to gain a better understanding of diplomacy and international relations. This Friday's meeting will serve to compile contact information of foreign ambassadors to the US, and to start assigning countries to pairs of students. Because the interviews will take place in pairs, we strongly encourage that both you and your partner attend Friday&#8217;s meeting. The groups that help to compile the contact information on Friday will have the first pick of the country whose ambassador they will contact and interview. Preliminary research of your choices of consideration is strongly suggested. Email TJTED at tjtechnocrats@gmail.com to get the project description handout, if you missed the interest meeting, or if you have any questions.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2662</id>
		<title>One Question Committee</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p class="MsoNormal"><span style="font-family:Arial, sans-serif;">Hi everyone! The One Question steering committee is looking for new members to join and help with upcoming activities related to the One Question. </span><span style="font-family:Tahoma, sans-serif;"></span></p><p></p><p class="Ms
]]>
			<![CDATA[
oNormal"><span style="font-family:Arial, sans-serif;"><br /> The One Question this year is: </span><em><span style="font-family:Arial, sans-serif;color:rgb(51,51,51);">&#8220;How can we strive to discover and pursue our own passions despite societal norms and external pressures that would compromise our aspirations and dissuade us from pursuing them?&#8221;</span></em><i><span style="font-family:Arial, sans-serif;color:rgb(51,51,51);"><br /><br /></span></i><span style="font-family:Arial, sans-serif;">The One Question steering committee is brainstorming ways to make this question more relevant and exciting to the TJ community, so participation and input would be fantastic! In the future, we are planning to invite speakers to TJ and host 8th period blocks for the One Question, so come out and help make an impact at TJ! The One Question steering committee meets on Monday 8th periods. </span></p><p></p><p class="MsoNormal"><span style="font-family:Arial, sans-serif;"></span></p><span style="font-family:Arial, sans-serif;">If you are interested in joining the One Question steering committee or have any questions regarding it, please contact Mrs. Sandstrom at <a href="mailto:ecsandstrom@fcps.edu">ecsandstrom@fcps.edu</a> or Brandon Kim at <a href="mailto:nodnarb44mik@gmail.com">nodnarb44mik@gmail.com</a></span>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Hi everyone! The One Question steering committee is looking for new members to join and help with upcoming activities related to the One Question.  The One Question this year is: &#8220;How can we strive to discover and pursue our own passions despite societal norms and external pressures that would compromise our aspirations and dissuade us from pursuing them?&#8221;The One Question steering committee is brainstorming ways to make this question more relevant and exciting to the TJ community, so participation and input would be fantastic! In the future, we are planning to invite speakers to TJ and host 8th period blocks for the One Question, so come out and help make an impact at TJ! The One Question steering committee meets on Monday 8th periods.   If you are interested in joining the One Question steering committee or have any questions regarding it, please contact Mrs. Sandstrom at ecsandstrom@fcps.edu or Brandon Kim at nodnarb44mik@gmail.com
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2658</id>
		<title>Name the TJ Commons - Vote Now</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
Students: <div><br /></div><div><div>Thank you for nominating hundreds of names for our TJ commons.  From this list of pioneers in various fields a committee of students, teachers, and administrators has narrowed the list down to the final 30 pioneers who represent various fields of study, historical time periods, and backgrounds.  What each of these selections have in common is that they are pioneers in their fields and demonstrate the ingenuity and innovativeness that we strive for here at TJ.  </div><div><br /></div><div>Please <a href="https://docs.google.com/a/fcpsschools.net/forms/d/1krWnnO05_MtL5E7fmYW1YFQcZzltRzU1jUbSf18QvYg/viewform">vote for the 14 pioneers</a> you would like for us to name TJ commons spaces after.  Each student and faculty member will be allowed to submit their top 14 list only once.  Voting will end on Oct. 31 at noon and the announcement of the winners will be made on the first week of November.</div><div><br /></div><div>Voting will be done through your fcpsschools.net Google Account.  Remember this is your Student ID Number with @fcpsschools.net at the end.  If you are having problems accessing your account please see Mrs. Applin or Mrs. Carpenter in the Library or Mrs. Tecuci in room 110 for help.  All students have a FCPS Google Account access.</div><div><br /></div><div><a href="https://docs.google.com/a/fcpsschools.net/forms/d/1krWnnO05_MtL5E7fmYW1YFQcZzltRzU1jUbSf18QvYg/viewform">VOTE HERE</a></div><div><br /></div><div><div>The Nominees</div><div><br /></div><div>JOHN BARDEEN </div><div><br /></div><div>He was an American physicist and electrical engineer and the only person to have won the Nobel Prize in Physics twice. The transistor revolutionized the electronics industry, allowing the Information Age to occur, and made possible the development of almost every modern electronic device, from telephones to computers to missiles. Bardeen's developments in superconductivity, which won him his second Nobel, are used in Nuclear Magnetic Resonance Spectroscopy (NMR) or its medical sub-tool magnetic resonance imaging (MRI).</div><div><br /></div><div>RACHEL CARSON <span class="Apple-tab-span" style="white-space:pre;"></span></div><div><br /></div><div>She was a writer, scientist, and ecologist who wrote many literary works to inform the public about nature, such as the book Silent Spring, in which she wrote about the dangerous effects of pesticides and tried to convince people to view the world in a different perspective. In 1963, she testified in front of Congress and called for policies to protect human health and the environment. She should be honored at TJ because she helped start the environmental revolution and changed the way we look at our world.</div><div><br /></div><div>GEORGE WASHINGTON CARVER <span class="Apple-tab-span" style="white-space:pre;"></span></div><div><br /></div><div>African-American inventor who had the highest number of patents at his time solely for the benefit of food consumption. He was a pioneer in all fields of science: chemistry, physics, botany and biology.</div><div><br /></div><div>VINT CERF </div><div><br /></div><div>He is a 'father of the Internet,' and, along with Bob Khan, created TCP/IP, the Transmission Control and Internet Protocols, the basis of the technology which would help create the Internet. He has connections to TJHSST (his son attended TJ) and has won numerous awards including the National Medal of Technology, the Turing Award, and the Presidential Medal of Freedom.</div><div><br /></div><div>JACQUES COUSTEAU </div><div><br /></div><div>He once described a scientist as 'a curious man looking through a keyhole, the keyhole of nature, trying to know what's going on.' Cousteau was passionate about the sea, and I admire him for using his talents in writing and film-making to draw much-needed attention to ocean conservation.</div><div><br /></div><div>MARIE CURIE </div><div><br /></div><div>She is an exemplar and a pioneer for not only science, but also women in science. As the first woman to win a Nobel Prize and the first person-- and only woman-- to win the Nobel Prize twice, she risked her life to bring forth breakthrough theories on radioactivity (a term she coined) and would ultimately pass away due to her extensive exposure to radiation, the epitome of scientific dedication until the end.</div><div><br /></div><div>LEONARDO DA VINCI </div><div><br /></div><div>The definition of a Renaissance man, da Vinci was not only famous for his art, but also for his work with anatomy, engineering, geology, botany, cartography, architecture, music, and mathematics.  I can think of no better person to represent the various interests that can be found at TJ.</div><div><br /></div><div>CHARLES DARWIN </div><div><br /></div><div>Without Darwin's theory of evolution by natural selection, biology is just a collection of facts without a unifying theory. As Theodosius Dobzhansky said in his 1973 essay: 'Nothing in Biology Makes Sense Except in the Light of Evolution'.</div><div><br /></div><div><br /></div><div>ALBERT EINSTEIN </div><div><br /></div><div>Einstein was above everyone else in that he didn't simply accept other scientists' theories. After discovering that the speed of light remains constant, he spent years researching its correlations with speed and mass and eventually reached a breakthrough where he discovered relativity.</div><div><br /></div><div>LEONHARD EULER </div><div><br /></div><div>He and Carl Friedrich Gauss vie for the title of greatest mathematician of all time. Euler contributed more than any other person to the field of mechanics (both fluid and solid).</div><div><br /></div><div>MICHAEL FARADAY <span class="Apple-tab-span" style="white-space:pre;"></span></div><div><br /></div><div>Michael Faraday displayed the true spirit of science even though he lacked a formal education. Faraday made many important discoveries about electricity, which helped create the world we live in today. I think we should name our commons the 'Faraday Commons' to honor this genius who so truly deserves it.</div><div><br /></div><div>BENJAMIN FRANKLIN </div><div><br /></div><div>Franklin was a self-made entrepreneur, turned renaissance man, turned patriot, who, embraced the best scientific and political elements of the Enlightenment.  His wisdom and cunning helped give birth to the United States as a society that made real the fantasy of popular government in an organic form that would facilitate, however slowly, the incubation and evolution of ideas such as justice and scientific advancement.</div><div><br /></div><div>ROSALIND FRANKLIN </div><div><br /></div><div>Though Franklin was instrumental in the discovery of DNA's structure, she received no credit for it at the time. Even now, she is frequently excluded from the 'Watson and Crick' narrative. I think it's important that we recognize the contributions of those often left out of lists of scientific pioneers and that we include female scientists and Rosalind Franklin fulfills both of those criteria.</div><div><br /></div><div>GALILEO GALLILEI </div><div><br /></div><div>The father of modern astronomy who supported the advancement of science against the persecution of the church (there were widely different belief systems in the early 17th century).</div><div><br /></div><div>MAHATMA GANDHI </div><div><br /></div><div>Despite the fact that Gandhi was an extremely well educated lawyer, he was a pioneer in the field of non-violent social activism. He is a reminder to us all that we must use our education to create a difference in the world, and due to the fact that we are recieving a world-class education it is our duty to become the leaders of tomorrow and take the baton to be the next Gandhis, because there is so much change that still needs to occur.</div><div><br /></div><div>CARL FRIEDRICH GAUSS </div><div><br /></div><div>His contemporaries called him princeps mathematicorum, prince of mathematics. We can call a mere lobby by his name.</div><div><br /></div><div>GRACE HOPPER</div><div><br /></div><div>As a female pioneer in the computing field, Rear Admiral Dr. Grace Murray Hopper was a remarkable woman who contributed to the transition from primitive programming techniques to the use of sophisticated compilers.  A mathematician, military officer, and computer scientist, she is an amazing role model for women.  Her belief that that the statement 'we've always done it that way' is not necessarily a good reason to continue to follow the status quo is an ideal that could inspire TJ students for many years to come.</div><div><br /></div><div>MAE JEMISON <span class="Apple-tab-span" style="white-space:pre;"></span></div><div><br /></div><div>A physician who became the first female African American astronaut and first black women to go into space.</div><div><br /></div><div>FRANK LLOYD WRIGHT<span class="Apple-tab-span" style="white-space:pre;"></span></div><div><br /></div><div>Innovative American Architect.</div><div><br /></div><div>JOHN LOCKE </div><div><br /></div><div>Locke thought of ideas that incredibly affected the founding of the US. His theories on government and the social contract were vital to Thomas Jefferson when he wrote the Declaration of Independence.</div><div><br /></div><div>THURGOOD MARSHALL <span class="Apple-tab-span" style="white-space:pre;"></span></div><div><br /></div><div>Lawyer-Changed history in 1954 when he successfully argued Brown vs. the Board of Education before the Supreme Court. Also played huge role in NAACP cases and was selected as first African-American Supreme Court Justice.</div><div><br /></div><div>ISAAC NEWTON <span class="Apple-tab-span" style="white-space:pre;"></span></div><div><br /></div><div>All TJ students will grow to hate this guy for inventing two of the most terrifying things ever: calculus and physics. It is both fitting and hilarious that Newton's name be integrated within the very foundation of TJ.</div><div><br /></div><div>ALFRED NOBEL</div><div><br /></div><div>Chemist who invented dynamite, and then dedicated his fortune to the Nobel Prizes out of remorse. A reminder to students of the power of knowledge to heal and to destroy.</div><div><br /></div><div>JACKIE ROBINSON </div><div><br /></div><div>Jackie Robinson was the first black player in the Major Baseball League. His entry faced tremendous turmoil in the 40s from 'separate but equal' advocates, yet his participation illustrated good players, regardless of race, could enhance professional sports.</div><div><br /></div><div>DAVID SAWYER </div><div><br /></div><div>Dr. Sawyer was the essential person who worked with business, government, and community organizations to launch TJHSST in 1984. In only 30 years, the school has maintained an international prominence, thanks to his vision and determination as assistant superintendent in Fairfax County Public Schools.</div><div><br /></div><div>NIKOLA TESLA </div><div><br /></div><div>Nikola Tesla is a name forgotten in history for no apparent reason even after his research in Alternating Current, Radio, and Energy Transmission. An immigrant undaunted by failing mental conditions, Tesla exemplifies the classic 'rags-to-riches' tale, going from digging ditches at $2 a day to powering the World's Fair at Niagara Falls.</div><div><br /></div><div>HENRY DAVID THOREAU </div><div><br /></div><div>A scientist, a philosopher, and the inspiration for the 'Civil Disobedience' of Martin Luther King, Thoreau challenges conformity and embodies the questioning spirit we hope TJ represents.  As he stated in his letter to a friend, H.G.O. Blake, on 16 November 1857: &#8220;It is not enough to be industrious; so are the ants. What are you industrious about?&#8221;</div><div><br /></div><div>ALAN TURING <span class="Apple-tab-span" style="white-space:pre;"></span></div><div><br /></div><div>Turing is widely considered to be the father of theoretical computer science and artificial intelligence. He provided formal definitions for the concepts of algorithm and computation, and conceived the 'Turing Machine' which helped win WWII.</div><div><br /></div><div>ORVILLE AND WILBUR WRIGHT </div><div><br /></div><div>The world has changed as a result of flying aircraft. The Wright brothers not only invented through experimentation, but they were daring enough to test the prototype vehicles themselves. Great role models for inquiry at Jefferson.</div><div><br /></div><div>MALALA YOUSAFZAI <span class="Apple-tab-span" style="white-space:pre;"></span></div><div><br /></div><div>Malala Yousafzai is a Pakistani activist for female education and the youngest-ever Nobel Prize recipient.</div></div><div><br /></div><div><a href="https://docs.google.com/a/fcpsschools.net/forms/d/1krWnnO05_MtL5E7fmYW1YFQcZzltRzU1jUbSf18QvYg/viewform">VOTE HERE</a></div></div><div><br /></div>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Students: Thank you for nominating hundreds of names for our TJ commons.  From this list of pioneers in various fields a committee of students, teachers, and administrators has narrowed the list down to the final 30 pioneers who represent various fields of study, historical time periods, and backg
]]>
			<![CDATA[
rounds.  What each of these selections have in common is that they are pioneers in their fields and demonstrate the ingenuity and innovativeness that we strive for here at TJ.  Please vote for the 14 pioneers you would like for us to name TJ commons spaces after.  Each student and faculty member will be allowed to submit their top 14 list only once.  Voting will end on Oct. 31 at noon and the announcement of the winners will be made on the first week of November.Voting will be done through your fcpsschools.net Google Account.  Remember this is your Student ID Number with @fcpsschools.net at the end.  If you are having problems accessing your account please see Mrs. Applin or Mrs. Carpenter in the Library or Mrs. Tecuci in room 110 for help.  All students have a FCPS Google Account access.VOTE HEREThe NomineesJOHN BARDEEN He was an American physicist and electrical engineer and the only person to have won the Nobel Prize in Physics twice. The transistor revolutionized the electronics industry, allowing the Information Age to occur, and made possible the development of almost every modern electronic device, from telephones to computers to missiles. Bardeen's developments in superconductivity, which won him his second Nobel, are used in Nuclear Magnetic Resonance Spectroscopy (NMR) or its medical sub-tool magnetic resonance imaging (MRI).RACHEL CARSON She was a writer, scientist, and ecologist who wrote many literary works to inform the public about nature, such as the book Silent Spring, in which she wrote about the dangerous effects of pesticides and tried to convince people to view the world in a different perspective. In 1963, she testified in front of Congress and called for policies to protect human health and the environment. She should be honored at TJ because she helped start the environmental revolution and changed the way we look at our world.GEORGE WASHINGTON CARVER African-American inventor who had the highest number of patents at his time solely for the benefit of food consumption. He was a pioneer in all fields of science: chemistry, physics, botany and biology.VINT CERF He is a 'father of the Internet,' and, along with Bob Khan, created TCP/IP, the Transmission Control and Internet Protocols, the basis of the technology which would help create the Internet. He has connections to TJHSST (his son attended TJ) and has won numerous awards including the National Medal of Technology, the Turing Award, and the Presidential Medal of Freedom.JACQUES COUSTEAU He once described a scientist as 'a curious man looking through a keyhole, the keyhole of nature, trying to know what's going on.' Cousteau was passionate about the sea, and I admire him for using his talents in writing and film-making to draw much-needed attention to ocean conservation.MARIE CURIE She is an exemplar and a pioneer for not only science, but also women in science. As the first woman to win a Nobel Prize and the first person-- and only woman-- to win the Nobel Prize twice, she risked her life to bring forth breakthrough theories on radioactivity (a term she coined) and would ultimately pass away due to her extensive exposure to radiation, the epitome of scientific dedication until the end.LEONARDO DA VINCI The definition of a Renaissance man, da Vinci was not only famous for his art, but also for his work with anatomy, engineering, geology, botany, cartography, architecture, music, and mathematics.  I can think of no better person to represent the various interests that can be found at TJ.CHARLES DARWIN Without Darwin's theory of evolution by natural selection, biology is just a collection of facts without a unifying theory. As Theodosius Dobzhansky said in his 1973 essay: 'Nothing in Biology Makes Sense Except in the Light of Evolution'.ALBERT EINSTEIN Einstein was above everyone else in that he didn't simply accept other scientists' theories. After discovering that the speed of light remains constant, he spent years researching its correlations with speed and mass and eventually reached a breakthrough where he discovered relativity.LEONHARD EULER He and Carl Friedrich Gauss vie for the title of greatest mathematician of all time. Euler contributed more than any other person to the field of mechanics (both fluid and solid).MICHAEL FARADAY Michael Faraday displayed the true spirit of science even though he lacked a formal education. Faraday made many important discoveries about electricity, which helped create the world we live in today. I think we should name our commons the 'Faraday Commons' to honor this genius who so truly deserves it.BENJAMIN FRANKLIN Franklin was a self-made entrepreneur, turned renaissance man, turned patriot, who, embraced the best scientific and political elements of the Enlightenment.  His wisdom and cunning helped give birth to the United States as a society that made real the fantasy of popular government in an organic form that would facilitate, however slowly, the incubation and evolution of ideas such as justice and scientific advancement.ROSALIND FRANKLIN Though Franklin was instrumental in the discovery of DNA's structure, she received no credit for it at the time. Even now, she is frequently excluded from the 'Watson and Crick' narrative. I think it's important that we recognize the contributions of those often left out of lists of scientific pioneers and that we include female scientists and Rosalind Franklin fulfills both of those criteria.GALILEO GALLILEI The father of modern astronomy who supported the advancement of science against the persecution of the church (there were widely different belief systems in the early 17th century).MAHATMA GANDHI Despite the fact that Gandhi was an extremely well educated lawyer, he was a pioneer in the field of non-violent social activism. He is a reminder to us all that we must use our education to create a difference in the world, and due to the fact that we are recieving a world-class education it is our duty to become the leaders of tomorrow and take the baton to be the next Gandhis, because there is so much change that still needs to occur.CARL FRIEDRICH GAUSS His contemporaries called him princeps mathematicorum, prince of mathematics. We can call a mere lobby by his name.GRACE HOPPERAs a female pioneer in the computing field, Rear Admiral Dr. Grace Murray Hopper was a remarkable woman who contributed to the transition from primitive programming techniques to the use of sophisticated compilers.  A mathematician, military officer, and computer scientist, she is an amazing role model for women.  Her belief that that the statement 'we've always done it that way' is not necessarily a good reason to continue to follow the status quo is an ideal that could inspire TJ students for many years to come.MAE JEMISON A physician who became the first female African American astronaut and first black women to go into space.FRANK LLOYD WRIGHT	Innovative American Architect.JOHN LOCKE Locke thought of ideas that incredibly affected the founding of the US. His theories on government and the social contract were vital to Thomas Jefferson when he wrote the Declaration of Independence.THURGOOD MARSHALL Lawyer-Changed history in 1954 when he successfully argued Brown vs. the Board of Education before the Supreme Court. Also played huge role in NAACP cases and was selected as first African-American Supreme Court Justice.ISAAC NEWTON All TJ students will grow to hate this guy for inventing two of the most terrifying things ever: calculus and physics. It is both fitting and hilarious that Newton's name be integrated within the very foundation of TJ.ALFRED NOBELChemist who invented dynamite, and then dedicated his fortune to the Nobel Prizes out of remorse. A reminder to students of the power of knowledge to heal and to destroy.JACKIE ROBINSON Jackie Robinson was the first black player in the Major Baseball League. His entry faced tremendous turmoil in the 40s from 'separate but equal' advocates, yet his participation illustrated good players, regardless of race, could enhance professional sports.DAVID SAWYER Dr. Sawyer was the essential person who worked with business, government, and community organizations to launch TJHSST in 1984. In only 30 years, the school has maintained an international prominence, thanks to his vision and determination as assistant superintendent in Fairfax County Public Schools.NIKOLA TESLA Nikola Tesla is a name forgotten in history for no apparent reason even after his research in Alternating Current, Radio, and Energy Transmission. An immigrant undaunted by failing mental conditions, Tesla exemplifies the classic 'rags-to-riches' tale, going from digging ditches at $2 a day to powering the World's Fair at Niagara Falls.HENRY DAVID THOREAU A scientist, a philosopher, and the inspiration for the 'Civil Disobedience' of Martin Luther King, Thoreau challenges conformity and embodies the questioning spirit we hope TJ represents.  As he stated in his letter to a friend, H.G.O. Blake, on 16 November 1857: &#8220;It is not enough to be industrious; so are the ants. What are you industrious about?&#8221;ALAN TURING Turing is widely considered to be the father of theoretical computer science and artificial intelligence. He provided formal definitions for the concepts of algorithm and computation, and conceived the 'Turing Machine' which helped win WWII.ORVILLE AND WILBUR WRIGHT The world has changed as a result of flying aircraft. The Wright brothers not only invented through experimentation, but they were daring enough to test the prototype vehicles themselves. Great role models for inquiry at Jefferson.MALALA YOUSAFZAI Malala Yousafzai is a Pakistani activist for female education and the youngest-ever Nobel Prize recipient.VOTE HERE
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2651</id>
		<title>
Parking Spaces Still Available for Seniors & Juniors
</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<span style="font-size:13px;font-family:arial, sans, sans-serif;">We still have some open parking spaces available. Students who have been previously been denied parking passes due to having 6 to 8 8th period absences will now be considered for these remaining spaces on a probationary status. Deadline to submit and application is Oct. 31. Applications should be submitted to the security office. These additional parking passes will be distributed on Nov. 5. Any questions, see Mr. McCormick or Mr. Hanson in the security office.<br /><br /></span>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
We still have some open parking spaces available. Students who have been previously been denied parking passes due to having 6 to 8 8th period absences will now be considered for these remaining spaces on a probationary status. Deadline to submit and application is Oct. 31. Applications should be submitted to the security office. These additional parking passes will be distributed on Nov. 5. Any questions, see Mr. McCormick or Mr. Hanson in the security office.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2646</id>
		<title>Why Do You Love Science?</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
L'Oreal would not be able to create the beauty products we all use and love - shampoos, mascara, lipsticks, and lotions - without our talented scientists and engineers, many of them women. L'Oreal is looking for young women who are interested in these fields. The National Girls Collaborative Project and L'Oreal USA invites high school girls in the Washington D.C. area to share why they love science using art, poetry, and/or multimedia. Twenty girls will then be selected to attend the L'Oreal USA For Women in Science Awards Ceremony in November where they will get to meet the 5 amazing female scientists being recognized at the ceremony. Share your love of STEM today! <a href="http://bit.ly/whydoyoulovescience">http://bit.ly/whydoyoulovescience</a>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
L'Oreal would not be able to create the beauty products we all use and love - shampoos, mascara, lipsticks, and lotions - without our talented scientists and engineers, many of them women. L'Oreal is looking for young women who are interested in these fields. The National Girls Collaborative Project and L'Oreal USA invites high school girls in the Washington D.C. area to share why they love science using art, poetry, and/or multimedia. Twenty girls will then be selected to attend the L'Oreal USA For Women in Science Awards Ceremony in November where they will get to meet the 5 amazing female scientists being recognized at the ceremony. Share your love of STEM today! http://bit.ly/whydoyoulovescience
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2638</id>
		<title>2014 Sadies Dance and Candy Grams</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p> The annual Sadie Hawkins Dance (girls ask guys) will be October 24th after the football game till 11:30. There will be music, a movie, and dancing! Tickets will be sold for $5 at the door and in advance. If you buy your ticket during pre-sale, 20th till the 24th, during Asking Week, you get a free Ghostie Gram. </p><p> Asking Week will be October 20th - 24th! </p><p> Ghostie Grams will be on sale in the Senior Lounge (Rm. 128) for $1.50 each or 3 for $4 from October 16th till the 28th. </p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
The annual Sadie Hawkins Dance (girls ask guys) will be October 24th after the football game till 11:30. There will be music, a movie, and dancing! Tickets will be sold for $5 at the door and in advance. If you buy your ticket during pre-sale, 20th till the 24th, during Asking Week, you get a free Ghostie Gram. Asking Week will be October 20th - 24th! Ghostie Grams will be on sale in the Senior Lounge (Rm. 128) for $1.50 each or 3 for $4 from October 16th till the 28th.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2637</id>
		<title>Bake Sale Nutritional Guidelines</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
Dear clubs,<div><br /> In Mr. Struck&#8217;s email to clubs, he promised a simplified version of the bake sale nutritional guidelines. <a href="https://iodine.tjhsst.edu/~2016jwoglom/uploads/NutritionGuidelines-10102014.pdf">Here they are!</a> We promise these are much easier to follow and still provide delicious options. Clubs that hold bake sales that do not adhere to these guidelines will lose bake sale privileges.<br /><br /></div><div> Love,<br /> TJ SGA </div>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Dear clubs, In Mr. Struck&#8217;s email to clubs, he promised a simplified version of the bake sale nutritional guidelines. Here they are! We promise these are much easier to follow and still provide delicious options. Clubs that hold bake sales that do not adhere to these guidelines will lose bake sale privileges. Love, TJ SGA
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2634</id>
		<title>TjTODAY: Smart Snacks</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p> TjTODAY is covering student reactions to the new USDA health guidelines. <a href="http://tinyurl.com/tjSmartSnacks">Take this super quick poll and tell us what you think! It&#8217;s just six yes or no questions!</a></p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
TjTODAY is covering student reactions to the new USDA health guidelines. Take this super quick poll and tell us what you think! It&#8217;s just six yes or no questions!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2626</id>
		<title>
Action Required: Google Apps for Education Account Setup
</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p><b>Important!</b> All Juniors and Seniors must activate their Google Apps for Education and take a survey confirming that they have done it by <u>Oct. 20.</u></p><p><b style="color:#FF0000;font-size:14px;">If you are seeing this message, you have either NOT activated GAE, or activated GAE but have NOT taken the survey and must do so.</b></p><p>Activation can only be done from a teacher computer, and also resets your FCPS Network password (which you need to do every year to be able to use the wireless networks on your personal device). Go to any of your teachers, the library, or room 110 to complete activation.</p><p>The survey requires an FCPS Google Apps account login. It can be taken from any computer once you have completed activation. <b><a href="http://tinyurl.com/GAEdone">The survey can be found here.</a></b></p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Important! All Juniors and Seniors must activate their Google Apps for Education and take a survey confirming that they have done it by Oct. 20. If you are seeing this message, you have either NOT activated GAE, or activated GAE but have NOT taken the survey and must do so. Activation can only be done from a teacher computer, and also resets your FCPS Network password (which you need to do every year to be able to use the wireless networks on your personal device). Go to any of your teachers, the library, or room 110 to complete activation. The survey requires an FCPS Google Apps account login. It can be taken from any computer once you have completed activation. The survey can be found here.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2621</id>
		<title>Student Tech Assistants</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
Interested in helping with technology maintenance at TJ? We will primarily provide level one technology assistance and support for the computer technology equipment in the school. Typical tasks include help with tv and vcr/dvd connections, projector displays, computers not working, checking mobile l
]]>
			<![CDATA[
aptop carts and printers. In addition, we will assist in moving, installing, connecting and setting up equipment, installing components in computers, checking for computers/laptops in need of repair, testing and fixing network drops, etc. Looking for those with the willingness to accept and follow direction, ability to work independently, perform physical labor, work collaboratively with other students, and able to finish tasks to completion is desired. No tech experience required. Sign up on Intranet for 8A Monday and Wednesdays! Email <a href="mailto:bkphillips@fcps.edu">techteam@tjhsst.edu</a> with questions.
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Interested in helping with technology maintenance at TJ? We will primarily provide level one technology assistance and support for the computer technology equipment in the school. Typical tasks include help with tv and vcr/dvd connections, projector displays, computers not working, checking mobile laptop carts and printers. In addition, we will assist in moving, installing, connecting and setting up equipment, installing components in computers, checking for computers/laptops in need of repair, testing and fixing network drops, etc. Looking for those with the willingness to accept and follow direction, ability to work independently, perform physical labor, work collaboratively with other students, and able to finish tasks to completion is desired. No tech experience required. Sign up on Intranet for 8A Monday and Wednesdays! Email techteam@tjhsst.edu with questions.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2615</id>
		<title>Homecoming Week + Dance Updates!</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p> The Annual Homecoming Dance is this Saturday, 8-11pm at TJ! Dance Tickets go on sale this week during lunches in the Junior Lounge/ Planetarium Lobby! They are on a SPECIAL price of $10 Monday, Tuesday, &amp; Wednesday and will be sold for $20 on Thursday, Friday, and at the door the day of the dance on Saturday. </p><p> Reminder: Homecoming Dance Guest Forms are due Wednesday at 3:50pm to the main office or <a href="mailto:sga.tjhsst@gmail.com">sga.tjhsst@gmail.com</a>. Hardcopies of the form can be found in the main office or an electronic copy can be found in a previous intranet post. </p><p><b>Homecoming Spirit Week is THIS week (9/22-9/26).</b> The Daily Spirit Days are as follows:</p> MONDAY - "Date Night" aka Dress Your Best<br /> TUESDAY - "Opposite Day" aka Pair up with someone and dress the opposite<br /> WEDNESDAY- "We are uNITEd" aka Group Day<br /> THURSDAY - Class-y Night aka Class Theme Day (Seniors "Hollywood Nights", Juniors "A Knight in Shining Armor", Sophomores "Back in the Day", Freshmen "Starry Night", Faculty "Friday Night Lights")<br /> FRIDAY - "Independence Day" aka Class Color Day (Seniors: Toga, Juniors: Blue, Sophomores: White, Freshmen: Red) <p> Be sure to head over to the daily pep rallies held in Gym 1 during break Monday through Thursday to cheer your heart out! </p><p> The Annual Homecoming Money Wars begins this Monday! Support your class' homecoming efforts and the "Iraqi Children Foundation" charity by donating money into lockers 615-618 (the old physics hallway i.e. middle hallway downstairs). Seniors donate to locker 615, Juniors to 616, Sophomores to 617, and Freshmen to 618. </p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
The Annual Homecoming Dance is this Saturday, 8-11pm at TJ! Dance Tickets go on sale this week during lunches in the Junior Lounge/ Planetarium Lobby! They are on a SPECIAL price of $10 Monday, Tuesday, &amp; Wednesday and will be sold for $20 on Thursday, Friday, and at the door the day of the dance on Saturday. Reminder: Homecoming Dance Guest Forms are due Wednesday at 3:50pm to the main office or sga.tjhsst@gmail.com. Hardcopies of the form can be found in the main office or an electronic copy can be found in a previous intranet post. Homecoming Spirit Week is THIS week (9/22-9/26). The Daily Spirit Days are as follows: MONDAY - "Date Night" aka Dress Your Best TUESDAY - "Opposite Day" aka Pair up with someone and dress the opposite WEDNESDAY- "We are uNITEd" aka Group Day THURSDAY - Class-y Night aka Class Theme Day (Seniors "Hollywood Nights", Juniors "A Knight in Shining Armor", Sophomores "Back in the Day", Freshmen "Starry Night", Faculty "Friday Night Lights") FRIDAY - "Independence Day" aka Class Color Day (Seniors: Toga, Juniors: Blue, Sophomores: White, Freshmen: Red) Be sure to head over to the daily pep rallies held in Gym 1 during break Monday through Thursday to cheer your heart out! The Annual Homecoming Money Wars begins this Monday! Support your class' homecoming efforts and the "Iraqi Children Foundation" charity by donating money into lockers 615-618 (the old physics hallway i.e. middle hallway downstairs). Seniors donate to locker 615, Juniors to 616, Sophomores to 617, and Freshmen to 618.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2614</id>
		<title>Exchange Students</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>TJHSST is seeking families to host students from the Ewell Castle School in Surry, England from October 22 &#8211; 26. Hosting an &#8220;exchange student&#8221; is a terrific experience that provides your student an opportunity to learn about the similarities and differences of students from a different country. In addition, the Ewell Castle School is hoping to arrange a return trip for students of hosting families. </p><p>Link to the Ewell Castle School website: <a href="http://www.ewellcastle.co.uk/">http://www.ewellcastle.co.uk/</a></p><p>If you are interested or have any questions, <a href="mailto:tjhsstengland@gmail.com">please contact Denise Castaldo at tjhsstengland@gmail.com</a>.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
TJHSST is seeking families to host students from the Ewell Castle School in Surry, England from October 22 &#8211; 26. Hosting an &#8220;exchange student&#8221; is a terrific experience that provides your student an opportunity to learn about the similarities and differences of students from a different country. In addition, the Ewell Castle School is hoping to arrange a return trip for students of hosting families. Link to the Ewell Castle School website: http://www.ewellcastle.co.uk/ If you are interested or have any questions, please contact Denise Castaldo at tjhsstengland@gmail.com.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2612</id>
		<title>College and Career Center Summer Senior Survey</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p><b>SENIORS -- Summer Survey 2014: </b> Seniors, please fill out the Summer Survey so that other students looking for summer opportunities can benefit from your experience. Please go to the survey link at: <a href="https://docs.google.com/a/fcpsschools.net/forms/d/1kFupjlbBsz12cylruh9-5RXuRvWDrlAbFiitJZsq0T8/viewform">https://docs.google.com/a/fcpsschools.net/forms/d/1kFupjlbBsz12cylruh9-5RXuRvWDrlAbFiitJZsq0T8/viewform</a></p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
SENIORS -- Summer Survey 2014: Seniors, please fill out the Summer Survey so that other students looking for summer opportunities can benefit from your experience. Please go to the survey link at: https://docs.google.com/a/fcpsschools.net/forms/d/1kFupjlbBsz12cylruh9-5RXuRvWDrlAbFiitJZsq0T8/viewform
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2611</id>
		<title>Join TJ Media!</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Want to write for the newspaper? Take photos for the yearbook? Shoot video for broadcast? Want to do it all? You're in luck: all of TJ Media's award-winning, nationally recognized publications now meet during 8th period. Sign up for TJ Media Wednesday (A or B) or Friday (A) for an interest meeting. You'll find out everything TJ Media has to offer and then some!</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Want to write for the newspaper? Take photos for the yearbook? Shoot video for broadcast? Want to do it all? You're in luck: all of TJ Media's award-winning, nationally recognized publications now meet during 8th period. Sign up for TJ Media Wednesday (A or B) or Friday (A) for an interest meeting. You'll find out everything TJ Media has to offer and then some!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2608</id>
		<title>Lost and Found Objects at TJ</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
Hot tips! Label the inside of your textbooks with &#8220;your name&#8221; AND &#8220;2014-15&#8221; so that our community can try to get them back to you if they get mislaid. (You don&#8217;t want to face the $$ fine if it never turns up!) ALSO, put a file onto your flashdrive with this file name: &#8220;YOUR NAME&#8217;s FLASH DRIVE&#8221; AND try to label the outside of it with a sharpie or metallic pen ( the librarians have one!) Where is our lost and found this year? It depends upon the object. <ul><li>All BOOKS go to the library's computer lab room 242B. (Sometimes binders and school papers go there, too.)</li><li>Precious objects such as flash drives, eyeglasses and jewelry go to the security office.</li><li>Everything else like found clothing, lunch bags, and water bottles go into the bins inside Gym 2.</li></ul>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Hot tips! Label the inside of your textbooks with &#8220;your name&#8221; AND &#8220;2014-15&#8221; so that our community can try to get them back to you if they get mislaid. (You don&#8217;t want to face the $$ fine if it never turns up!) ALSO, put a file onto your flashdrive with this file name: &#8220;YOUR NAME&#8217;s FLASH DRIVE&#8221; AND try to label the outside of it with a sharpie or metallic pen ( the librarians have one!) Where is our lost and found this year? It depends upon the object. All BOOKS go to the library's computer lab room 242B. (Sometimes binders and school papers go there, too.) Precious objects such as flash drives, eyeglasses and jewelry go to the security office. Everything else like found clothing, lunch bags, and water bottles go into the bins inside Gym 2.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2605</id>
		<title>Homecoming Dance + Guest Forms</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Hey TJ! Don't forget that Homecoming Week is the fourth week of school (September 22-26) and ASKING WEEK is NEXT WEEK (September 15-19). Get your ask on, TJ! </p><p> This year's Homecoming Dance will take place at TJ on Saturday, September 27th from 8-11pm. Tickets will be sold from September 22-26 during lunch in J-Lounge/ Planetarium Lobby for $10 Monday through Wednesday and $20 on Thursday and Friday. They will also be sold at the door for $20. </p><p> If you would like to bring a non-TJ guest to the dance, please fill out <b><a href="https://www.tjhsst.edu/~2016jwoglom/uploads/2014%20Guest%20Form.docx">this form</a></b> (hard copies available in the Main Office) and return electronically to sga.tjhsst@gmail.com or the Main Office by BY 4PM on Wednesday, September 24th (no exceptions!) Remember, this is NOT a form you can fill out in the last minute, so plan ahead! </p><p> On Thursday, September 25th, a list of all approved guests will be posted outside the Activities Office in the AudLob. If your guest's name is not on the list, they may NOT attend the dance. </p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Hey TJ! Don't forget that Homecoming Week is the fourth week of school (September 22-26) and ASKING WEEK is NEXT WEEK (September 15-19). Get your ask on, TJ! This year's Homecoming Dance will take place at TJ on Saturday, September 27th from 8-11pm. Tickets will be sold from September 22-26 during lunch in J-Lounge/ Planetarium Lobby for $10 Monday through Wednesday and $20 on Thursday and Friday. They will also be sold at the door for $20. If you would like to bring a non-TJ guest to the dance, please fill out this form (hard copies available in the Main Office) and return electronically to sga.tjhsst@gmail.com or the Main Office by BY 4PM on Wednesday, September 24th (no exceptions!) Remember, this is NOT a form you can fill out in the last minute, so plan ahead! On Thursday, September 25th, a list of all approved guests will be posted outside the Activities Office in the AudLob. If your guest's name is not on the list, they may NOT attend the dance.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2602</id>
		<title>
NEW Administrative Detention POLICY (formerly Lost and Found):
</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<span>In the first two weeks, you will have a homeroom session to LEARN ABOUT 8th PERIOD SIGN UP AND ATTENDANCE POLICIES. </span><span>I want to alert you to some significant changes to 8th period Lost and Found. First, we changed the name to Administrative Detention.  Second, we moved to a quarter based system. Administrative Detention remains a double block activity for students with unexcused (uncleared) 8<sup>th</sup> period absences.<span></span>Periodically each quarter, a report of 8th period unexcused absences is run, and following the criteria below, students will be assigned to Administrative Detention during 8<sup>th</sup> period.<span></span></span><span style="font-size:10pt;font-family:Symbol;letter-spacing:-.1pt;"><span><br /><br /><span style="font:7pt 'Times New Roman';"></span></span></span><b><u><span style="letter-spacing:-.1pt;">If a student gets 2 or more absences in any QUARTER</span></u></b><span style="letter-spacing:-.1pt;">, they will be assigned to Administrative Detention (AD)</span><span style="font-size:10pt;font-family:Symbol;"><span><br /><span style="font:7pt 'Times New Roman';"></span></span></span><b><u><span>If a student gets any additional absences</span></u></b><span> in the SAME quarter after attending AD that quarter, they will be assigned to the next Administrative Detention.</span><span style="letter-spacing:-.1pt;"></span><span><br /><br />Students will receive an email at their TJ email address letting them know and giving them a deadline to fix any mistakes with their teacher(s).  If the absences are not cleared in time, the student will be assigned to a double block of Detention.  Students may not be excused from Detention for any reason and failure to show up for the whole period will result in a referral to the grade level administrator.</span><br /><br />While assignment to AD is now based upon your quarterly attendance, <i><span>absences are recorded for the year and DO NOT disappear after attending Administrative Detention.  </span></i><span><span></span>Yearly totals are used for referrals (as outlined below), assigning leadership, mentorship, parking and other privileges.<span></span></span><span></span><b><span><br /><br />PLEASE NOTE: Students will get referred to an Assistant Principal (for possible additional consequences and/or Saturday detention) if any of the following apply:</span></b><p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-top:6pt;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:1in;text-indent:-.25in;"><span style="font-size:10pt;font-family:Symbol;"><span>-<span style="font:7pt 'Times New Roman';"></span></span></span><span>failure to show up for the detention period</span><span style="font-size:10pt;font-family:Symbol;"><span><br /></span></span></p><p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-top:6pt;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:1in;text-indent:-.25in;"><span style="font-size:10pt;font-family:Symbol;"><span>-<span style="font:7pt 'Times New Roman';"></span></span></span>getting <b><u>5</u></b> or more absences in any quarter</p><span><b><i></i></b></span><p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-top:6pt;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:1in;text-indent:-.25in;"><span style="font-size:10pt;font-family:Symbol;"><span>-<span style="font:7pt 'Times New Roman';"></span></span></span><span>getting assigned to <b><u>3</u></b> Administrative Detentions in the <b><i>year</i></b></span></p><span style="font-size:10pt;font-family:Symbol;"><span></span></span><p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-top:6pt;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:1in;text-indent:-.25in;"><span style="font-size:10pt;font-family:Symbol;"><span>-<span style="font:7pt 'Times New Roman';"></span></span></span><span>getting <b><u>10</u></b> or more absences in the <b><i>year</i></b></span></p><p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-left:.5in;"><span><span style="font-size:11pt;">If you have any questions, please come see us in the 8th period office. </span></span></p><p class="MsoNormal"></p><span style="font-size:10pt;"></span><b><span></span></b>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
In the first two weeks, you will have a homeroom session to LEARN ABOUT 8th PERIOD SIGN UP AND ATTENDANCE POLICIES. I want to alert you to some significant changes to 8th period Lost and Found. First, we changed the name to Administrative Detention.  Second, we moved to a quarter based system. Admi
]]>
			<![CDATA[
nistrative Detention remains a double block activity for students with unexcused (uncleared) 8th period absences.  Periodically each quarter, a report of 8th period unexcused absences is run, and following the criteria below, students will be assigned to Administrative Detention during 8th period.           If a student gets 2 or more absences in any QUARTER, they will be assigned to Administrative Detention (AD)         If a student gets any additional absences in the SAME quarter after attending AD that quarter, they will be assigned to the next Administrative Detention.Students will receive an email at their TJ email address letting them know and giving them a deadline to fix any mistakes with their teacher(s).  If the absences are not cleared in time, the student will be assigned to a double block of Detention.  Students may not be excused from Detention for any reason and failure to show up for the whole period will result in a referral to the grade level administrator.While assignment to AD is now based upon your quarterly attendance, absences are recorded for the year and DO NOT disappear after attending Administrative Detention.  Yearly totals are used for referrals (as outlined below), assigning leadership, mentorship, parking and other privileges.   PLEASE NOTE: Students will get referred to an Assistant Principal (for possible additional consequences and/or Saturday detention) if any of the following apply: -      failure to show up for the detention period-      getting 5 or more absences in any quarter-      getting assigned to 3 Administrative Detentions in the year -      getting 10 or more absences in the year If you have any questions, please come see us in the 8th period office.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2597</id>
		<title>
			<span style="color: red; weight: bold">Final First-Day Schedules</span>
		</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Final first-day schedules are now loaded into Intranet. No more schedule changes will be made before the first day of school.</p><p>You MUST attend the classes listed on Intranet and in the email you will receive for the first day of school and unless/until you are specifically instructed otherwise by a Counselor or the Director of Student Services.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Final first-day schedules are now loaded into Intranet. No more schedule changes will be made before the first day of school. You MUST attend the classes listed on Intranet and in the email you will receive for the first day of school and unless/until you are specifically instructed otherwise by a Counselor or the Director of Student Services.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2548</id>
		<title>self-paced EPF course</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p class="MsoNormal">The Economics and Personal Finance (EPF) self-paced online option is now available to students during the 2014-2015 school year if it is taken as a 7th course (students in grades 9-12) or as an 8th course (only students in grades 9-11 who do not have academic intervention plans).  <br /></p><p class="MsoNormal">This course is self-paced and self-directed.  All material is available on FCPS 24/7.  The student must be self-motivated and able to fulfill the requirements without a teacher to direct and assist with studies.  The student must fulfill the stated schedule.  A teacher will not be available to explain the material.  The student must have the ability to follow the schedule and take the tests when due on his/her own.  No reminders will be sent to inform the student of due dates.  Progress reports will be sent to students, parents, and counselors.  All grades are available in FCPS 24/7 and it is the student&#8217;s responsibility to check those and stay on target.   Student must have a working computer, access to the internet along with access to FCPS 24/7, and valid email addresses for himself/herself and parent/guardian.  All communication will be via email and FCPS 24/7. </p><p class="MsoNormal"><span style="font-size:13px;">The cost for the course is $100 and there is only a Pass or Fail designated outcome.  Students should see their counselor <a href="http://www.tjhsst.edu/~emglazer/Fall-EPF-SelfPacedFinal4.pdf">with the registration form</a> and submit it no later than September 24.  Note the form says September 26, but we need the extra days for processing within TJ before FCPS.</span></p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
The Economics and Personal Finance (EPF) self-paced online option is now available to students during the 2014-2015 school year if it is taken as a 7th course (students in grades 9-12) or as an 8th course (only students in grades 9-11 who do not have academic intervention plans).   This course is self-paced and self-directed.  All material is available on FCPS 24/7.  The student must be self-motivated and able to fulfill the requirements without a teacher to direct and assist with studies.  The student must fulfill the stated schedule.  A teacher will not be available to explain the material.  The student must have the ability to follow the schedule and take the tests when due on his/her own.  No reminders will be sent to inform the student of due dates.  Progress reports will be sent to students, parents, and counselors.  All grades are available in FCPS 24/7 and it is the student&#8217;s responsibility to check those and stay on target.   Student must have a working computer, access to the internet along with access to FCPS 24/7, and valid email addresses for himself/herself and parent/guardian.  All communication will be via email and FCPS 24/7.  The cost for the course is $100 and there is only a Pass or Fail designated outcome.  Students should see their counselor with the registration form and submit it no later than September 24.  Note the form says September 26, but we need the extra days for processing within TJ before FCPS.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2456</id>
		<title>Have an invention to share?</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<div>The Tonight Show starring Jimmy Fallon contacted the school with interest to profile student inventors on their show in November.  They are looking for novel gadgets that can be used at home and the general public would find useful/entertaining.  </div><div><br /></div><div>Here are recent examples: <br /></div><div><div><p class="MsoNormal">     Part 1: <a href="http://youtu.be/53GyBD_ggpE">http://youtu.be/53GyBD_ggpE</a><br />     Part 2: <a href="http://youtu.be/lT10FOmOspg" style="font-size:10pt;">http://youtu.be/lT10FOmOspg</a><br />     Part 3: <a href="http://youtu.be/QfxHP2g-iUg" style="font-size:10pt;">http://youtu.be/QfxHP2g-iUg</a></p></div><div>Interested? We invite you to make a 1-2 minute video that showcases the inventor and invention. Keep it simple - you can use the video camera on a smartphone.</div><div><br /></div><div>Make sure the inventor says the following things:</div><div>--Name (first name)</div><div>--Age</div><div>--Hometown</div><div>--Invention Name</div><div>--How they got the idea for the invention</div><div>--Show how the invention works</div><div><br /></div><div>Send Dr. Glazer an email (emglazer@fcps.edu) if you have something to share, and he will forward your video.</div></div>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
The Tonight Show starring Jimmy Fallon contacted the school with interest to profile student inventors on their show in November.  They are looking for novel gadgets that can be used at home and the general public would find useful/entertaining.  Here are recent examples:      Part 1: http://youtu.be/53GyBD_ggpE     Part 2: http://youtu.be/lT10FOmOspg      Part 3: http://youtu.be/QfxHP2g-iUg Interested? We invite you to make a 1-2 minute video that showcases the inventor and invention. Keep it simple - you can use the video camera on a smartphone.Make sure the inventor says the following things:--Name (first name)--Age--Hometown--Invention Name--How they got the idea for the invention--Show how the invention worksSend Dr. Glazer an email (emglazer@fcps.edu) if you have something to share, and he will forward your video.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2593</id>
		<title>Food Donation Drive</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Hey TJ! During the last few days of school there will be a sandwich making session to make sandwiches for a local homeless shelter and a Construction Worker Party to help thank the workers for all of their hard work, but we need YOUR help! </p><p> We are asking for food donations to be dropped off by this Friday to Trailer 33 (right outside the J-Lounge)! <a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1qgCEsjKL1p3bQo2d5VP5LbMVfUjntjapYijReRIxkDM/edit">Look here for a specific list of what we need.</a></p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Hey TJ! During the last few days of school there will be a sandwich making session to make sandwiches for a local homeless shelter and a Construction Worker Party to help thank the workers for all of their hard work, but we need YOUR help! We are asking for food donations to be dropped off by this Friday to Trailer 33 (right outside the J-Lounge)! Look here for a specific list of what we need.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2590</id>
		<title>Summer Assignments</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
Summer Assignments are available at <a href="http://www.tjhsst.edu/summer-assignments/index.html">tjhsst.edu/summer-assignments</a>. Have a great summer (after finals)!
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Summer Assignments are available at tjhsst.edu/summer-assignments. Have a great summer (after finals)!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2589</id>
		<title>Honor Council Election Results!</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p> Congratulations to your Honor Council Members for the 2014-2015 school year! </p> Class of 2015: Anant Das (returning), Muhamad Ihssan, Ellen Kan, and Rhea Sharma<br /> Class of 2016: Peter Andringa, Milan Bharadwaj, Sophia Moses (returning), and Sahana Ramani<br /> Class of 2017: Numan Khan, Kristin Myers (returning), and Mina Nowroozi
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Congratulations to your Honor Council Members for the 2014-2015 school year! Class of 2015: Anant Das (returning), Muhamad Ihssan, Ellen Kan, and Rhea Sharma Class of 2016: Peter Andringa, Milan Bharadwaj, Sophia Moses (returning), and Sahana Ramani Class of 2017: Numan Khan, Kristin Myers (returning), and Mina Nowroozi
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2587</id>
		<title>TODAY ONLY! Do you have ZERO 8th period Absences?</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<br />Yes?  Fantastic!! Stop by the wrestling room for a treat from 2:05 - 2:20!<br /><br />Thanks!<br />Mrs. Burch<br />
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Yes?  Fantastic!! Stop by the wrestling room for a treat from 2:05 - 2:20!Thanks!Mrs. Burch
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2586</id>
		<title>BigSibs Applications</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Hey TJ! Do you want to help the incoming freshmen have a smooth start to their high school experience and make them feel welcome as part of the TJ community? </p><p>If so, please apply to be a BigSib! This year, the selection process will be more selective to make the program as successful as possible, so please make sure you can make a commitment to be engaged and enthusiastic for your Little Sib's entire high school career. </p><p><a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1CZv61FL5Foo8Tth5af6jpSioJAatw8OpjKhDN5WuQXU/viewform?usp=send_form">Before applying, please fill out this interest form, and further instructions on applying will be sent to you.</a></p><p> Applications can be found at <a href="http://www.tjhsst.edu/bigsibs">tjhsst.edu/bigsibs</a> and are due on Monday, June 16th. If you have any questions, please <a href="mailto:tjbigsibs@gmail.com">feel free to contact us at tjbigsibs@gmail.com</a>. Thank you so much! </p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Hey TJ! Do you want to help the incoming freshmen have a smooth start to their high school experience and make them feel welcome as part of the TJ community? If so, please apply to be a BigSib! This year, the selection process will be more selective to make the program as successful as possible, so please make sure you can make a commitment to be engaged and enthusiastic for your Little Sib's entire high school career. Before applying, please fill out this interest form, and further instructions on applying will be sent to you. Applications can be found at tjhsst.edu/bigsibs and are due on Monday, June 16th. If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us at tjbigsibs@gmail.com. Thank you so much!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2583</id>
		<title>Summer School Course Requests</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
Some students have been requesting to take two summer school courses.  This is an exception to the normal guidelines of one course, however the administration recognizes there are mitigating circumstances where this option would create flexibility for students. A second summer course will be permitted only through an appeal conference with the principal (contact cmlove@fcps.edu for a 15 minute appointment).  <div><br /></div><div>Consideration will be given only to students who are taking the self-paced Pass-Fail EPF course (see previous announcement for details), have a four year plan for review (submit as an email attachment), and are taking a semester class OR plan to pursue a curricular area in depth that would otherwise not be possible without taking this 2nd summer course (e.g., four years of performing arts, paired with the neuroscience research course sequence).</div>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Some students have been requesting to take two summer school courses.  This is an exception to the normal guidelines of one course, however the administration recognizes there are mitigating circumstances where this option would create flexibility for students. A second summer course will be permitted only through an appeal conference with the principal (contact cmlove@fcps.edu for a 15 minute appointment).  Consideration will be given only to students who are taking the self-paced Pass-Fail EPF course (see previous announcement for details), have a four year plan for review (submit as an email attachment), and are taking a semester class OR plan to pursue a curricular area in depth that would otherwise not be possible without taking this 2nd summer course (e.g., four years of performing arts, paired with the neuroscience research course sequence).
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2581</id>
		<title>Student Government Election Results!</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p> Congratulations to your student government leaders for the 2014-2015 school year! </p> SGA:<br /> President: Anant Das (2015)<br /> Vice-President: Dennis Kim (2015)<br /> Secretary: Parsa Zand (2015)<br /> Treasurer: Andrew Howard (2016)<br /><br /> Student Advisory Council (SAC): Seniors Sreya Atluri and William Liu, Sophomore Shohini Gupta, and Freshman Anshu Sharma<br /><br /> Class of 2015:<br /> President: Danial Hussain<br /> Vice-President: Puneeth Uttla<br /> Secretary: Nan Baker<br /> Treasurer: Nihar Gudiseva<br /> Co-Historians: Arthur He and Helen Zhang<br /> Senator: Jenny Kim<br /><br /> Class of 2016:<br /> President: Kunal Naik<br /> Vice-President: James Park<br /> Secretary: Sophia Moses<br /> Treasurer: Spencer Weiss<br /> Co-Historians: Will Ryu and Christina Wei<br /> Senator: Kaila Stein<br /><br /> Class of 2017:<br /> President: Laura Chu<br /> Vice-President: Devan Kowdley<br /> Secretary: Justin Lee<br /> Treasurer: Subul Malik<br /> Co-Historians: Caroline Nguyen and Abhishek Mogili<br /> Senator: Giancarlo Veldetaro<br />
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Congratulations to your student government leaders for the 2014-2015 school year! SGA: President: Anant Das (2015) Vice-President: Dennis Kim (2015) Secretary: Parsa Zand (2015) Treasurer: Andrew Howard (2016) Student Advisory Council (SAC): Seniors Sreya Atluri and William Liu, Sophomore Shohini Gupta, and Freshman Anshu Sharma Class of 2015: President: Danial Hussain Vice-President: Puneeth Uttla Secretary: Nan Baker Treasurer: Nihar Gudiseva Co-Historians: Arthur He and Helen Zhang Senator: Jenny Kim Class of 2016: President: Kunal Naik Vice-President: James Park Secretary: Sophia Moses Treasurer: Spencer Weiss Co-Historians: Will Ryu and Christina Wei Senator: Kaila Stein Class of 2017: President: Laura Chu Vice-President: Devan Kowdley Secretary: Justin Lee Treasurer: Subul Malik Co-Historians: Caroline Nguyen and Abhishek Mogili Senator: Giancarlo Veldetaro
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2576</id>
		<title>Help with Physicals</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>TJ Students, Ms Murphy and Ms Hudak need your help! </p><p>We need students to help with physicals. You would helping with data entry and helping with students moving from one station to the other. Sign up with your friends! Get community service hours! Here is a chance to give back to the athletic training program! To volunteer, go to <a href="http://www.fcps.edu/sports">www.fcps.edu/sports</a> and follow the Sports PPE links.</p> Thank you! --Ms Murphy and Ms Hudak
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
TJ Students, Ms Murphy and Ms Hudak need your help! We need students to help with physicals. You would helping with data entry and helping with students moving from one station to the other. Sign up with your friends! Get community service hours! Here is a chance to give back to the athletic training program! To volunteer, go to www.fcps.edu/sports and follow the Sports PPE links. Thank you! --Ms Murphy and Ms Hudak
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2567</id>
		<title>Library</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Students who wish to visit the library MUST bring a pass from their teacher. Even if you are just popping in to print. No pass/no entry&#8212;sorry! (Remind your teachers of this need before you come all the way here.) Thanks! </p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Students who wish to visit the library MUST bring a pass from their teacher. Even if you are just popping in to print. No pass/no entry&#8212;sorry! (Remind your teachers of this need before you come all the way here.) Thanks!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2565</id>
		<title>
Juniors! Last chance to turn in Busch Gardens Forms!
</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p> Hey Juniors! Only a limited amount of spots left on the Busch Gardens trip, be sure to submit payment and forms to Room 129 TODAY! Message an officer or email tjhsst.2015@gmail.com with questions! Forms: http://bit.ly/BGForms</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Hey Juniors! Only a limited amount of spots left on the Busch Gardens trip, be sure to submit payment and forms to Room 129 TODAY! Message an officer or email tjhsst.2015@gmail.com with questions! Forms: http://bit.ly/BGForms
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2557</id>
		<title>TJ Partnership Fund at tjSTAR</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>The TJ Partnership Fund needs student videographers to film the tjSTAR reception, taking place at the McLean Hilton on Thursday, May 29th from 6:00 - 8:00 pm. Please respond to <a href="mailto:scourtney@fcps.edu">scourtney@fcps.edu</a> by Tuesday, May 27th if you're available and interested.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
The TJ Partnership Fund needs student videographers to film the tjSTAR reception, taking place at the McLean Hilton on Thursday, May 29th from 6:00 - 8:00 pm. Please respond to scourtney@fcps.edu by Tuesday, May 27th if you're available and interested.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2556</id>
		<title>J-Day Basketball</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Not participating in J-Day Basketball but want to get in on the hype? Submit a completed bracket with your name and grade on the top right corner by noon this Friday 5/23 to Trailer 33 for a chance to be crowned winner of the May Madness 2014 Bracket Challenge (there will be a prize!!!). WOTS is that Warren Buffett received his inspiration to create his Million Dollar Bracket Challenge from this May Madness itself. <a href="https://docs.google.com/file/d/0B7IEunr2_iS7UVNNcVhSMFY0OWs/edit">Don't miss out</a>. <span style="color:rgb(2,2,2);font-size:10pt;">(</span><a href="http://tinyurl.com/jday2014" style="font-family:'Open Sans', Arial, Helvetica, Roboto, 'Droid Sans', sans-serif;font-size:10pt;">Rosters, seeds, game schedule can be found here</a><span style="color:rgb(2,2,2);font-size:10pt;">)</span></p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Not participating in J-Day Basketball but want to get in on the hype? Submit a completed bracket with your name and grade on the top right corner by noon this Friday 5/23 to Trailer 33 for a chance to be crowned winner of the May Madness 2014 Bracket Challenge (there will be a prize!!!). WOTS is that Warren Buffett received his inspiration to create his Million Dollar Bracket Challenge from this May Madness itself. Don't miss out. (Rosters, seeds, game schedule can be found here)
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2555</id>
		<title>Candy Grams</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>With the Class of 2014 having only a few weeks left at TJ, did you just realize how much you're going to miss your senior friends? Do you have a senior crush that you've been too scared to say anything about? Do you have any words or confessions that you've been too shy to tell a senior about? Would you like to send your graduating friends a sweet gift? Well now is your chance!</p><p>On May 27, 29, and 30 during lunch in Room 129. Seniors, Juniors, and Underclassmen can buy candy grams to be delivered to seniors on June 2nd. Candy grams may be anonymous and are $1.00 each or eleven for $10.00. Candy options are Skittles and Hershey Bars. </p><p>If you would like to fill out forms ahead of time, <a href="http://bit.ly/2014SeniorCandyGramForm">feel free to use this form</a>. You can write all over, on the back, and attach as much additional paper as you need! If you have any special requests to go along with the delivery of your candy gram, let us know when you pay! </p> Sponsored by the Class of 2015
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
With the Class of 2014 having only a few weeks left at TJ, did you just realize how much you're going to miss your senior friends? Do you have a senior crush that you've been too scared to say anything about? Do you have any words or confessions that you've been too shy to tell a senior about? Would you like to send your graduating friends a sweet gift? Well now is your chance! On May 27, 29, and 30 during lunch in Room 129. Seniors, Juniors, and Underclassmen can buy candy grams to be delivered to seniors on June 2nd. Candy grams may be anonymous and are $1.00 each or eleven for $10.00. Candy options are Skittles and Hershey Bars. If you would like to fill out forms ahead of time, feel free to use this form. You can write all over, on the back, and attach as much additional paper as you need! If you have any special requests to go along with the delivery of your candy gram, let us know when you pay! Sponsored by the Class of 2015
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2554</id>
		<title>Junior Class Amusement Park Trip</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p> Hey Juniors! It's finally time for the Annual Junior Class Amusement Park Field Trip! This year we are going to Busch Gardens on Monday, June 23rd! The price of the trip is $80 and your admission ticket and a trip to and from the park is included in that package. More details are on the information form. </p><p> You can pick up forms from the box inside Room 129 or find them all at the link below. They are due to the box in Room 129 by THIS FRIDAY, May 23rd. Please contact <a href="mailto:tjhsst.2015@gmail.com">tjhsst.2015@gmail.com</a> or an officer with any questions!</p><p>Forms: <a href="http://bit.ly/BGForms">http://bit.ly/BGForms</a></p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Hey Juniors! It's finally time for the Annual Junior Class Amusement Park Field Trip! This year we are going to Busch Gardens on Monday, June 23rd! The price of the trip is $80 and your admission ticket and a trip to and from the park is included in that package. More details are on the information form. You can pick up forms from the box inside Room 129 or find them all at the link below. They are due to the box in Room 129 by THIS FRIDAY, May 23rd. Please contact tjhsst.2015@gmail.com or an officer with any questions! Forms: http://bit.ly/BGForms
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2553</id>
		<title>Class Council Elections</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<div><div>To make democracy work, we must be a nation of participants, not simply observers. Run to become a class officer in order to attain a valuable opportunity to lead and serve your class. The election packet can be found <a href="https://iodine.tjhsst.edu/docs/view/271">here</a>.</div><div><br /></div><div>Be sure to attend one of the following MANDATORY interest meetings taking place in T-33.</div><div><ul><li><span style="font-size:13px;">Friday 5/16 - Lunch/ A block</span><br /></li><li><span style="font-size:13px;">Tuesday 5/20 &#8211; Lunch</span><br /></li><li><span style="font-size:13px;">Wednesday 5/21&#8211; B block</span><br /></li><li><span style="font-size:13px;">Friday 5/23-Lunch</span><br /></li></ul></div></div>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
To make democracy work, we must be a nation of participants, not simply observers. Run to become a class officer in order to attain a valuable opportunity to lead and serve your class. The election packet can be found here.Be sure to attend one of the following MANDATORY interest meetings taking place in T-33.Friday 5/16 - Lunch/ A blockTuesday 5/20 &#8211; LunchWednesday 5/21&#8211; B blockFriday 5/23-Lunch
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2543</id>
		<title>tjSTAR Registration Information</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>The 2014 tjSTAR will take place on Wednesday, May 28th. The Symposium will feature presentations of amazing student research projects, guest professional speakers from the STEM community and exciting demonstrations and displays: Microstrategy&#8217;s smartphone-controlled vending machine, NASA&#8217;s Infrared Camera, Google Glass, Human Powered Submarines and more!. Registration for all sessions is now open. <b><a href="https://www.tjhsst.edu/students/activities/tjstar/registration/registration.php">Please go to the registration page here.</a></b> Don&#8217;t delay! Registration closes on Thursday, May 22nd.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
The 2014 tjSTAR will take place on Wednesday, May 28th. The Symposium will feature presentations of amazing student research projects, guest professional speakers from the STEM community and exciting demonstrations and displays: Microstrategy&#8217;s smartphone-controlled vending machine, NASA&#8217;s Infrared Camera, Google Glass, Human Powered Submarines and more!. Registration for all sessions is now open. Please go to the registration page here. Don&#8217;t delay! Registration closes on Thursday, May 22nd.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2541</id>
		<title>TEDxTJHSST Feedback Survey</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Thank you so much to everyone who came to TEDxTJHSST! Hopefully you enjoyed it and also learned a lot. If you attended the conference, we&#8217;d appreciate <a href="https://spreadsheets.google.com/viewform?formkey=dHFDUkZ2a2NCNTl6dmZoTEJQQU5PMXc6MQ&amp;entry_0=TEDxTJHSST&amp;entry_1=April+25,+2014">if you could spend a few minutes filling out this feedback survey</a> so we can make future conferences even better. Thanks again! </p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Thank you so much to everyone who came to TEDxTJHSST! Hopefully you enjoyed it and also learned a lot. If you attended the conference, we&#8217;d appreciate if you could spend a few minutes filling out this feedback survey so we can make future conferences even better. Thanks again!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2526</id>
		<title>Stress Less, Laugh More</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p class="MsoNormal">From April 28-May 2, celebrate <i>Stress Less, Laugh More</i> week.  Participate in l<span style="text-indent:-.25in;">arge-group yoga, l</span><span style="text-indent:-.25in;">augh yoga, m</span><span style="text-indent:-.25in;">indful meditation, meet t</span><span style="text-indent:-.25in;">herapy dog(s), watch m</span><span style="text-indent:-.25in;">ovies, play g</span><span style="text-indent:-.25in;">ames.  Self-care, downtime, reflection, and play are important when studying for your exams.</span></p><p class="MsoNormal"><img src="http://www.tjhsst.edu/~emglazer/stressless_laughmore.jpg" alt="stressless_laughmore.jpg" /><span style="text-indent:-.25in;"><br /></span></p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
From April 28-May 2, celebrate Stress Less, Laugh More week.  Participate in large-group yoga, laugh yoga, mindful meditation, meet therapy dog(s), watch movies, play games.  Self-care, downtime, reflection, and play are important when studying for your exams.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2518</id>
		<title>J-Day Forms</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Overwhelmed by the sudden influx of J-Day forms? <a href="http://tinyurl.com/jday2014">Find all information regarding J-Day at this link.</a> All forms are currently up and it will continue to be updated with booth maps, booth information, and performances! </p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Overwhelmed by the sudden influx of J-Day forms? Find all information regarding J-Day at this link. All forms are currently up and it will continue to be updated with booth maps, booth information, and performances!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2504</id>
		<title>J-Day May Madness</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>J-Day "May Madness" Basketball Tournament is rapidly approaching... Which one of you are willing to take the challenge to compete against arguably the most talented, cohesive basketball teams the world has ever seen? </p><p>Register your team <a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1eDTKXAFUllE2kqcFAgS7SH_2BDP4ycfsNGIMHZZVIPk/viewform">through this form</a> by Friday, May 2nd. All rules and regulations are outlined on the form. </p><p>Every team must pay a $5 entry fee to participate and every team member <a href="https://www.tjhsst.edu/~2016jwoglom/uploads/JDayBBallPermissionForm2014.docx">must turn in this parent permission form</a>. Bring forms to T-33 and turn it in to the appropriate folder on the SGA Bulletin Board to the right. All money MUST be handed directly to either Ms. Razzino or Mrs. Hurowitz. </p><p>Questions, comments, and concerns can be directed to tournament coordinator Jenny Kim or sga.tjhsst@gmail.com. </p><p>May the Madness Begin! </p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
J-Day "May Madness" Basketball Tournament is rapidly approaching... Which one of you are willing to take the challenge to compete against arguably the most talented, cohesive basketball teams the world has ever seen? Register your team through this form by Friday, May 2nd. All rules and regulations are outlined on the form. Every team must pay a $5 entry fee to participate and every team member must turn in this parent permission form. Bring forms to T-33 and turn it in to the appropriate folder on the SGA Bulletin Board to the right. All money MUST be handed directly to either Ms. Razzino or Mrs. Hurowitz. Questions, comments, and concerns can be directed to tournament coordinator Jenny Kim or sga.tjhsst@gmail.com. May the Madness Begin!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2500</id>
		<title>APUSH and AB Calc Practice Exams Canceled</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p> Unfortunately, due to low interest the Class of 2015 has canceled the practice AP US History and AB Calculus exams scheduled for Saturday, March 29 at TJ. If you have already paid for these tests, stop by room 129 next Friday during eighth period to be reimbursed. The Class of 2015 apologizes for any inconvenience. </p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Unfortunately, due to low interest the Class of 2015 has canceled the practice AP US History and AB Calculus exams scheduled for Saturday, March 29 at TJ. If you have already paid for these tests, stop by room 129 next Friday during eighth period to be reimbursed. The Class of 2015 apologizes for any inconvenience.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2482</id>
		<title>College And Career Center Info Sessions</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p><b>Summer Opportunities Info Session, Friday, A Block: </b>Rustic Pathways, which offers community service, language immersion and other experiential education programs for high school students all over the world, will be in giving a presentation in the CCC on Friday, March 14. The speaker is E
]]>
			<![CDATA[
rin Murphy. </p><p><b>Community Service Opportunity Info Session for Girls, Friday, B Block: </b> Learn about community service opportunities with ZONTA International, a worldwide organization dedicated to improving the status of women through service and advocacy in a presentation in the College Career Center on Friday, March 14, during B Block. The speaker is Carol Beechler.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Summer Opportunities Info Session, Friday, A Block: Rustic Pathways, which offers community service, language immersion and other experiential education programs for high school students all over the world, will be in giving a presentation in the CCC on Friday, March 14. The speaker is Erin Murphy. Community Service Opportunity Info Session for Girls, Friday, B Block: Learn about community service opportunities with ZONTA International, a worldwide organization dedicated to improving the status of women through service and advocacy in a presentation in the College Career Center on Friday, March 14, during B Block. The speaker is Carol Beechler.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2481</id>
		<title>Jefferson Consulting</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Jefferson Consulting wants to get your feedback on I-Night. <a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1Mhqf8GuU245gSJaGEjOH6qloqzatob3SwuwrVQeez9g/viewform">Please take three minutes to fill out the following survey</a>.</p> Thanks from:<br /> Jefferson Consulting: Serving TJ organizations through free consulting services
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Jefferson Consulting wants to get your feedback on I-Night. Please take three minutes to fill out the following survey. Thanks from: Jefferson Consulting: Serving TJ organizations through free consulting services
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2480</id>
		<title>Library Access during JLC</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Students, we really need your help. We are trying to keep the library open for your use during JLC. However, it is very sad to report that a student&#8217;s rudeness to one of our valuable JLC parent volunteers means that we&#8217;ve lost another one of them. We cannot keep the main library and library computer classrooms open during JLC without the supervision provided by our parent volunteers, so we have special &#8220;quiet study&#8221; rules for JLC mornings that really must be adhered to by all of our students. Do your part to make the volunteers feel respected, valued and thanked for their service to you while librarians are at meetings on JLC Thursdays. Please print at home Wednesday nights in case you do not get access to the library&#8217;s spaces during JLC. -- Mrs. Carpenter</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Students, we really need your help. We are trying to keep the library open for your use during JLC. However, it is very sad to report that a student&#8217;s rudeness to one of our valuable JLC parent volunteers means that we&#8217;ve lost another one of them. We cannot keep the main library and library computer classrooms open during JLC without the supervision provided by our parent volunteers, so we have special &#8220;quiet study&#8221; rules for JLC mornings that really must be adhered to by all of our students. Do your part to make the volunteers feel respected, valued and thanked for their service to you while librarians are at meetings on JLC Thursdays. Please print at home Wednesday nights in case you do not get access to the library&#8217;s spaces during JLC. -- Mrs. Carpenter
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2479</id>
		<title>Military Information Night at Robinson</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Military Information Night tonight, Robinson Secondary School, 7:00-9:00 p.m. : Interested in a career as a military officer? Come to Robinson Secondary School tonight to learn about attending West Point, the U.S. Naval Academy, the U.S. Air Force Academy, U.S. Coast Guard Academy and U.S. Merchant Marine Academy. ROTC reps will also be on hand to answer questions about ROTC programs and scholarships for college. (5305 Sideburn Rd. Fairfax, VA)</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Military Information Night tonight, Robinson Secondary School, 7:00-9:00 p.m. : Interested in a career as a military officer? Come to Robinson Secondary School tonight to learn about attending West Point, the U.S. Naval Academy, the U.S. Air Force Academy, U.S. Coast Guard Academy and U.S. Merchant Marine Academy. ROTC reps will also be on hand to answer questions about ROTC programs and scholarships for college. (5305 Sideburn Rd. Fairfax, VA)
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2474</id>
		<title>TEDxTJHSST Conference</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>TJ&#8217;s second TEDx conference will be held on April 25th during 6th, 7th, and 8th periods! Sign up for 8th period to hear inspiring talks by students, teachers, alumni, and parents related to our theme, &#8220;Overachieve: How do we surpass mediocrity in pursuing our passions?&#8221; 6th and 7th periods are open to class sign-up only, so ask your teachers to sign your classes up.</p><p>If you have a unique idea you would like to share at the conference, please <a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1cBRQhIxjpMPtf1hz0m5o8HEB6VZ7cApK82zZLE4FmLU/viewform">fill out this application by April 1st</a>. Please encourage parents and teachers to apply as well.</p><p>Please email tedxtjhsst14@gmail.com with any questions. TEDxTJHSST is an officially licensed event of TED.com. All talks will be recorded and posted on the TEDx website.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
TJ&#8217;s second TEDx conference will be held on April 25th during 6th, 7th, and 8th periods! Sign up for 8th period to hear inspiring talks by students, teachers, alumni, and parents related to our theme, &#8220;Overachieve: How do we surpass mediocrity in pursuing our passions?&#8221; 6th and 7th periods are open to class sign-up only, so ask your teachers to sign your classes up. If you have a unique idea you would like to share at the conference, please fill out this application by April 1st. Please encourage parents and teachers to apply as well. Please email tedxtjhsst14@gmail.com with any questions. TEDxTJHSST is an officially licensed event of TED.com. All talks will be recorded and posted on the TEDx website.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2466</id>
		<title>Active Science Alliance</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Do you miss doing exciting hands on projects? Do you want to put your newly learned physics/ other knowledge to the test? Are you free Friday A block and looking to go to a club thats exciting, and has food? If you answered yes to any of these questions come to Active Science Alliance this Friday A-block and join us in doing an egg drop lab! (free food will be provided!)</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Do you miss doing exciting hands on projects? Do you want to put your newly learned physics/ other knowledge to the test? Are you free Friday A block and looking to go to a club thats exciting, and has food? If you answered yes to any of these questions come to Active Science Alliance this Friday A-block and join us in doing an egg drop lab! (free food will be provided!)
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2462</id>
		<title>Lost and Found</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<span style="font-size:15px;"><font>LOST AND FOUND was been moved to Friday, March 14. </font><span></span><span>To be removed you must clear your 8th period absences BEFORE 4pm on March 12.</span><span></span>   Many February absences can still be cleared!</span><p> It's simple: click on the absence link from your home page, print the page and ask the teacher to sign off that you were there --  be sure to include the name of the activity that you actually attended.  Return the sheet to room 134 and you're done! </p><p> To keep from getting an absence:<b><br /></b></p><ul><li><b>Go to the activity that you chose -- and don't leave!</b></li><li>Make sure your teacher knows you are there.</li><li>DO NOT sign the bottom of a roster. These names are not included in attendance and will result in an absence. </li><li><b>Don't ask a <u>substitute</u> to 'call you in', they can't! Absences in activities with a substitute teacher cannot be cleared!</b><br /></li><li>If you forgot to sign up before the end of lunch, come to the 8th period office to get a pass</li><li>Turn in your pass to the sponsor as soon as you arrive! </li><li>QUESTIONS? See Mrs. Burch in the 8th period office (room 134)</li></ul>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
LOST AND FOUND was been moved to Friday, March 14.  To be removed you must clear your 8th period absences BEFORE 4pm on March 12.    Many February absences can still be cleared! It's simple: click on the absence link from your home page, print the page and ask the teacher to sign off that you were there --  be sure to include the name of the activity that you actually attended.  Return the sheet to room 134 and you're done! To keep from getting an absence:Go to the activity that you chose -- and don't leave!Make sure your teacher knows you are there.DO NOT sign the bottom of a roster. These names are not included in attendance and will result in an absence. Don't ask a substitute to 'call you in', they can't! Absences in activities with a substitute teacher cannot be cleared!If you forgot to sign up before the end of lunch, come to the 8th period office to get a passTurn in your pass to the sponsor as soon as you arrive! QUESTIONS? See Mrs. Burch in the 8th period office (room 134)
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2452</id>
		<title>Virginia High School League (VHSL) Scholarships</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Attention TJ Students: The Virginia High School League (VHSL) is offering 2 scholarships:</p><p>Allstate Scholarship: 4 scholarships: (1) Male Athlete, (1) Female Athlete, (1) Academic Activities student, (1) Courageous Achievement. Scholarships will be selected based on the following criteria</p> a. Candidates must have earned a Varsity letter<br /> b. A minimum grade point average of 3.0 on a 4.0 scale<br /> c. Involvement in other school activities outside of school (work, charities, etc)<br /> d. Two letters of support<br /> e. A maximum of 500-word typed student essay describing how extracurricular activities have enhanced his/her educational experience.<br /> f. A Head and Shoulder photograph <br /><p>Wells Fargo Citizenship Award: This scholarship provides $1000.00 dollars for (12) graduating seniors who wish to further their education at an institution of higher learning, including universities, colleges and trade schools. Scholarships will be selected based on the following criteria</p> a. Graduation at the end of the current school year<br /> b. Participation in at least one activity offered by the VHSL<br /> c. Contributions to family, school and community<br /> d. Promotion of good citizenship and sportsmanship<br /> e. Two letters of support, one from a school official and one from any other non- family member with knowledge of applicants contributions to citizenship<br /> f. Essay (must be typed and should be between 500-1000 words) by the student<br /> Applications should be submitted to the Career Center or Activities Office no later than March 7th <p>If you have any questions please contact Linda Kropf in the College Career Center or Rusty Hodges in the Activities Office</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Attention TJ Students: The Virginia High School League (VHSL) is offering 2 scholarships: Allstate Scholarship: 4 scholarships: (1) Male Athlete, (1) Female Athlete, (1) Academic Activities student, (1) Courageous Achievement. Scholarships will be selected based on the following criteria a. Candidates must have earned a Varsity letter b. A minimum grade point average of 3.0 on a 4.0 scale c. Involvement in other school activities outside of school (work, charities, etc) d. Two letters of support e. A maximum of 500-word typed student essay describing how extracurricular activities have enhanced his/her educational experience. f. A Head and Shoulder photograph Wells Fargo Citizenship Award: This scholarship provides $1000.00 dollars for (12) graduating seniors who wish to further their education at an institution of higher learning, including universities, colleges and trade schools. Scholarships will be selected based on the following criteria a. Graduation at the end of the current school year b. Participation in at least one activity offered by the VHSL c. Contributions to family, school and community d. Promotion of good citizenship and sportsmanship e. Two letters of support, one from a school official and one from any other non- family member with knowledge of applicants contributions to citizenship f. Essay (must be typed and should be between 500-1000 words) by the student Applications should be submitted to the Career Center or Activities Office no later than March 7th If you have any questions please contact Linda Kropf in the College Career Center or Rusty Hodges in the Activities Office
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2449</id>
		<title>Remaining INITE tickets sale on 2/27</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
Our INITE lottery is complete, and we estimate 200-300 tickets remain for the March 1 show. &nbsp;There will be one final sale on February 27 during JLC right outside the security office. &nbsp;At 8:10am, we will ask students to draw random numbers to determine their position in line, so there isn't a need to get to school any earlier than 8am. &nbsp;Tickets are $10 each, students may purchase up to 2 tickets, exact change is required, and a pledge form will be required as a promise not to resale the tickets.
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Our INITE lottery is complete, and we estimate 200-300 tickets remain for the March 1 show. &nbsp;There will be one final sale on February 27 during JLC right outside the security office. &nbsp;At 8:10am, we will ask students to draw random numbers to determine their position in line, so there isn't a need to get to school any earlier than 8am. &nbsp;Tickets are $10 each, students may purchase up to 2 tickets, exact change is required, and a pledge form will be required as a promise not to resale the tickets.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2447</id>
		<title>
College and Career Center - Engineering Week Info Session
</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Engineering Week is Feb. 16-22! Come to the College and Career Center on Wednesday, February 19, during either A or B Block to learn more about engineering careers from Dr. William Kilpatrick of the Society of American Military Engineers. Dr. Kilpatrick will be joined by engineering colleagues and GMU students in a discussion of the field of engineering. The speakers will also give information on engineering camps and scholarships.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Engineering Week is Feb. 16-22! Come to the College and Career Center on Wednesday, February 19, during either A or B Block to learn more about engineering careers from Dr. William Kilpatrick of the Society of American Military Engineers. Dr. Kilpatrick will be joined by engineering colleagues and GMU students in a discussion of the field of engineering. The speakers will also give information on engineering camps and scholarships.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2441</id>
		<title>College and Career Center Info Sessions</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p><b>Info Session on Summer internship with the Federal Government:</b> A representative from the Department of Agriculture will be in the College and Career Center on Wednesday during A Block to talk about a job shadowing day in March and summer internships at the Department of Agriculture.</p><p><b>Info Session on Global Public Service Academies for Health:</b> Students interested in a career in medicine, who would like to spend this summer working on public health projects in Latin America or the Caribbean, come to the College and Career Center during B Block on Wednesday to hear from TJ Junior, Sage Teasley, about Global Public Service Academies for Health.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Info Session on Summer internship with the Federal Government: A representative from the Department of Agriculture will be in the College and Career Center on Wednesday during A Block to talk about a job shadowing day in March and summer internships at the Department of Agriculture. Info Session o
]]>
			<![CDATA[
n Global Public Service Academies for Health: Students interested in a career in medicine, who would like to spend this summer working on public health projects in Latin America or the Caribbean, come to the College and Career Center during B Block on Wednesday to hear from TJ Junior, Sage Teasley, about Global Public Service Academies for Health.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2433</id>
		<title>What Can You Build in a Day?</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Remember HackTJ from last year? Well, get pumped for its bigger and better successor: PilotDC! PilotDC is a 24 hour event where you can bring your idea to life with help from the area's top engineers, designers, and entrepreneurs! With lots of free swag and free food too, <a href="http://dc.gopilot.org">be sure to check out http://dc.gopilot.org to sign up and learn more</a>! Don't know much about coding? No problem, beginners are welcome. Come and create an awesome app or website!</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Remember HackTJ from last year? Well, get pumped for its bigger and better successor: PilotDC! PilotDC is a 24 hour event where you can bring your idea to life with help from the area's top engineers, designers, and entrepreneurs! With lots of free swag and free food too, be sure to check out http://dc.gopilot.org to sign up and learn more! Don't know much about coding? No problem, beginners are welcome. Come and create an awesome app or website!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2430</id>
		<title>RTC Asking Week + Menchies Fundraiser</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>It's the week you've finally all been waiting for... RTC ASKING WEEK (Upperclassmen ask Underclassmen) from Monday, February 10th through Friday, February 14th!</p><p>Then stay after school on the 14th and head over to Menchies from 4-7pm and mention you're supporting "TJ 2015" to support the Junior Class while eating a sweet treat before you head to the Varsity Basketball Double-Header Senior-Night Game!</p><p>Please note that there is NO RTC dance this year. </p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
It's the week you've finally all been waiting for... RTC ASKING WEEK (Upperclassmen ask Underclassmen) from Monday, February 10th through Friday, February 14th! Then stay after school on the 14th and head over to Menchies from 4-7pm and mention you're supporting "TJ 2015" to support the Junior Class while eating a sweet treat before you head to the Varsity Basketball Double-Header Senior-Night Game! Please note that there is NO RTC dance this year.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2424</id>
		<title>Urinetown Production</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
Wanna be in an extra-curricular musical? We need actors, singers, dancers, instrumentalists and techies for our production of Urinetown May 2nd and 3rd. No experience necessary. <p></p><p>Auditions are after school on February 19 in the Performing Arts Wing. Prepare for your audition or just come and have fun at the Musical Theatre Workshop on February 11 &amp; 12, 4:00 &#8211; 6:00. Sign-up in the Performing Arts Wing.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Wanna be in an extra-curricular musical? We need actors, singers, dancers, instrumentalists and techies for our production of Urinetown May 2nd and 3rd. No experience necessary. Auditions are after school on February 19 in the Performing Arts Wing. Prepare for your audition or just come and have fun at the Musical Theatre Workshop on February 11 &amp; 12, 4:00 &#8211; 6:00. Sign-up in the Performing Arts Wing.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2423</id>
		<title>Exam Schedule</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<span style="font-size:12.0pt;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,&quot;serif&quot;; mso-fareast-font-family:Calibri;mso-fareast-theme-font:minor-latin;mso-ansi-language: EN-US;mso-fareast-language:EN-US;mso-bidi-language:AR-SA">Today (1-29-2014) we will run exam periods 5, 6, and 7 without a make-up period - (no 8th period). Students who need to schedule a make up exam should speak with their teachers about doing so in period 5, 6, or 7 where they are not scheduled to take an exam already. Bell schedule will be posted as soon as it is finalized.</span>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Today (1-29-2014) we will run exam periods 5, 6, and 7 without a make-up period - (no 8th period). Students who need to schedule a make up exam should speak with their teachers about doing so in period 5, 6, or 7 where they are not scheduled to take an exam already. Bell schedule will be posted as soon as it is finalized.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2417</id>
		<title>Updated Schedule for Semester Exams</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>A message from JEFFERSON HSST </p><p>Dear TJ community, </p><p>This afternoon, FCPS adjusted the end of semester exam calendar to a two-day period so classes can meet before exams are taken. As a result of this decision, please disregard the message about schedules sent at 11:10am this morning. Our schedule moving forward, regardless of inclement weather cancellations, will be:</p><br /> First day back (January 24): Blue (periods 1-4)<br /> Second day back&nbsp;<span style="font-size: 13px;">(January 27)</span>: Red (periods 5-8)<br /> Third day back: Blue exams<br /> Fourth day back: Red exams and make-up <p>I look forward to welcoming everyone back to school. </p><p>Goooooooooo Colonials!</p><p>Evan Glazer </p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
A message from JEFFERSON HSST Dear TJ community, This afternoon, FCPS adjusted the end of semester exam calendar to a two-day period so classes can meet before exams are taken. As a result of this decision, please disregard the message about schedules sent at 11:10am this morning. Our schedule moving forward, regardless of inclement weather cancellations, will be: First day back (January 24): Blue (periods 1-4) Second day back&nbsp;(January 27): Red (periods 5-8) Third day back: Blue exams Fourth day back: Red exams and make-up I look forward to welcoming everyone back to school. Goooooooooo Colonials!Evan Glazer
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2407</id>
		<title>8th period CHANGES today!</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[

			
			<!--[if gte mso 9]>
			<xml>
				<o:OfficeDocumentSettings>
					<o:AllowPNG/>
				</o:OfficeDocumentSettings>
			</xml>
			<![endif]--><span style="font-size:11.0pt;font-family:" calibri','sans-serif';="" mso-ascii-theme-font:minor-latin;mso-fareast-font-family:calibri;mso-fareast-theme-font:="" minor-latin;mso-hansi-
]]>
			<![CDATA[
theme-font:minor-latin;mso-bidi-font-family:'times="" new="" roman';="" mso-bidi-theme-font:minor-bidi;mso-ansi-language:en-us;mso-fareast-language:="" en-us;mso-bidi-language:ar-sa'="">With the recent moves of some staff, several 8<sup>th</sup> period activities have changed locations.<span style="mso-spacerun:yes">&nbsp; </span>Please double check the intranet to see if any changes affect your activities.<span style="mso-spacerun:yes">&nbsp; </span></span>
			<!--[if gte mso 9]>
			<xml>
				<w:WordDocument>
					<w:View>Normal</w:View>
					<w:Zoom>0</w:Zoom>
					<w:TrackMoves/>
					<w:TrackFormatting/>
					<w:PunctuationKerning/>
					<w:ValidateAgainstSchemas/>
					<w:SaveIfXMLInvalid>false</w:SaveIfXMLInvalid>
					<w:IgnoreMixedContent>false</w:IgnoreMixedContent>
					<w:AlwaysShowPlaceholderText>false</w:AlwaysShowPlaceholderText>
					<w:DoNotPromoteQF/>
					<w:LidThemeOther>EN-US</w:LidThemeOther>
					<w:LidThemeAsian>X-NONE</w:LidThemeAsian>
					<w:LidThemeComplexScript>X-NONE</w:LidThemeComplexScript>
					<w:Compatibility>
						<w:BreakWrappedTables/>
						<w:SnapToGridInCell/>
						<w:WrapTextWithPunct/>
						<w:UseAsianBreakRules/>
						<w:DontGrowAutofit/>
						<w:SplitPgBreakAndParaMark/>
						<w:EnableOpenTypeKerning/>
						<w:DontFlipMirrorIndents/>
						<w:OverrideTableStyleHps/>
					</w:Compatibility>
					<m:mathPr>
						<m:mathFont m:val='Cambria Math'/>
						<m:brkBin m:val='before'/>
						<m:brkBinSub m:val='&#45;-'/>
						<m:smallFrac m:val='off'/>
						<m:dispDef/>
						<m:lMargin m:val='0'/>
						<m:rMargin m:val='0'/>
						<m:defJc m:val='centerGroup'/>
						<m:wrapIndent m:val='1440'/>
						<m:intLim m:val='subSup'/>
						<m:naryLim m:val='undOvr'/>
					</m:mathPr>
				</w:WordDocument>
			</xml>
			<![endif]-->
			<!--[if gte mso 9]>
			<xml>
				<w:LatentStyles DefLockedState='false' DefUnhideWhenUsed='true' DefSemiHidden='true' DefQFormat='false' DefPriority='99' LatentStyleCount='267'>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='0' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' QFormat='true' Name='Normal'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='9' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' QFormat='true' Name='heading 1'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='9' QFormat='true' Name='heading 2'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='9' QFormat='true' Name='heading 3'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='9' QFormat='true' Name='heading 4'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='9' QFormat='true' Name='heading 5'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='9' QFormat='true' Name='heading 6'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='9' QFormat='true' Name='heading 7'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='9' QFormat='true' Name='heading 8'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='9' QFormat='true' Name='heading 9'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='39' Name='toc 1'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='39' Name='toc 2'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='39' Name='toc 3'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='39' Name='toc 4'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='39' Name='toc 5'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='39' Name='toc 6'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='39' Name='toc 7'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='39' Name='toc 8'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='39' Name='toc 9'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='35' QFormat='true' Name='caption'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='10' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' QFormat='true' Name='Title'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='1' Name='Default Paragraph Font'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='11' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' QFormat='true' Name='Subtitle'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='22' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' QFormat='true' Name='Strong'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='20' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' QFormat='true' Name='Emphasis'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='59' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Table Grid'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Placeholder Text'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='1' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' QFormat='true' Name='No Spacing'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='60' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light Shading'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='61' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light List'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='62' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light Grid'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='63' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Shading 1'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='64' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Shading 2'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='65' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium List 1'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='66' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium List 2'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='67' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 1'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='68' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 2'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='69' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 3'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='70' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Dark List'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='71' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful Shading'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='72' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful List'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='73' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful Grid'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='60' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light Shading Accent 1'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='61' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light List Accent 1'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='62' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light Grid Accent 1'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='63' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Shading 1 Accent 1'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='64' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Shading 2 Accent 1'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='65' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium List 1 Accent 1'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Revision'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='34' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' QFormat='true' Name='List Paragraph'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='29' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' QFormat='true' Name='Quote'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='30' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' QFormat='true' Name='Intense Quote'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='66' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium List 2 Accent 1'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='67' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 1 Accent 1'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='68' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 2 Accent 1'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='69' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 3 Accent 1'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='70' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Dark List Accent 1'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='71' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful Shading Accent 1'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='72' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful List Accent 1'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='73' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful Grid Accent 1'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='60' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light Shading Accent 2'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='61' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light List Accent 2'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='62' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light Grid Accent 2'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='63' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Shading 1 Accent 2'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='64' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Shading 2 Accent 2'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='65' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium List 1 Accent 2'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='66' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium List 2 Accent 2'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='67' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 1 Accent 2'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='68' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 2 Accent 2'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='69' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 3 Accent 2'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='70' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Dark List Accent 2'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='71' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful Shading Accent 2'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='72' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful List Accent 2'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='73' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful Grid Accent 2'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='60' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light Shading Accent 3'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='61' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light List Accent 3'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='62' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light Grid Accent 3'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='63' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Shading 1 Accent 3'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='64' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Shading 2 Accent 3'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='65' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium List 1 Accent 3'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='66' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium List 2 Accent 3'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='67' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 1 Accent 3'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='68' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 2 Accent 3'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='69' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 3 Accent 3'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='70' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Dark List Accent 3'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='71' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful Shading Accent 3'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='72' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful List Accent 3'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='73' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful Grid Accent 3'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='60' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light Shading Accent 4'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='61' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light List Accent 4'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='62' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light Grid Accent 4'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='63' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Shading 1 Accent 4'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='64' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Shading 2 Accent 4'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='65' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium List 1 Accent 4'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='66' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium List 2 Accent 4'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='67' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 1 Accent 4'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='68' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 2 Accent 4'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='69' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 3 Accent 4'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='70' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Dark List Accent 4'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='71' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful Shading Accent 4'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='72' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful List Accent 4'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='73' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful Grid Accent 4'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='60' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light Shading Accent 5'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='61' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light List Accent 5'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='62' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light Grid Accent 5'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='63' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Shading 1 Accent 5'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='64' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Shading 2 Accent 5'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='65' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium List 1 Accent 5'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='66' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium List 2 Accent 5'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='67' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 1 Accent 5'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='68' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 2 Accent 5'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='69' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 3 Accent 5'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='70' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Dark List Accent 5'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='71' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful Shading Accent 5'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='72' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful List Accent 5'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='73' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful Grid Accent 5'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='60' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light Shading Accent 6'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='61' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light List Accent 6'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='62' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Light Grid Accent 6'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='63' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Shading 1 Accent 6'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='64' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Shading 2 Accent 6'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='65' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium List 1 Accent 6'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='66' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium List 2 Accent 6'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='67' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 1 Accent 6'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='68' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 2 Accent 6'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='69' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Medium Grid 3 Accent 6'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='70' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Dark List Accent 6'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='71' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful Shading Accent 6'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='72' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful List Accent 6'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='73' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' Name='Colorful Grid Accent 6'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='19' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' QFormat='true' Name='Subtle Emphasis'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='21' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' QFormat='true' Name='Intense Emphasis'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='31' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' QFormat='true' Name='Subtle Reference'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='32' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' QFormat='true' Name='Intense Reference'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='33' SemiHidden='false' UnhideWhenUsed='false' QFormat='true' Name='Book Title'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='37' Name='Bibliography'/>
					<w:LsdException Locked='false' Priority='39' QFormat='true' Name='TOC Heading'/>
				</w:LatentStyles>
			</xml>
			<![endif]-->
			<!--[if gte mso 10]>
			<style> /* Style Definitions */ table.MsoNormalTable {mso-style-name:'Table Normal'; mso-tstyle-rowband-size:0; mso-tstyle-colband-size:0; mso-style-noshow:yes; mso-style-priority:99; mso-style-parent:''; mso-padding-alt:0in 5.4pt 0in 5.4pt; mso-para-margin:0in; mso-para-margin-bottom:.0001pt; mso-pagination:widow-orphan; font-size:11.0pt; font-family:'Calibri','sans-serif'; mso-ascii-font-family:Calibri; mso-ascii-theme-font:minor-latin; mso-hansi-font-family:Calibri; mso-hansi-theme-font:minor-latin;} </style>
			<![endif]-->
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
With the recent moves of some staff, several 8th period activities have changed locations.&nbsp; Please double check the intranet to see if any changes affect your activities.&nbsp;
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2320</id>
		<title>LOST & FOUND Friday</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<span style="font-size: 15px">LOST AND FOUND list is FRIDAY!&nbsp; To be removed you must clear your 8th period absences BEFORE 4pm today.</span><p> It's simple: click on the absence link from your home page, print the page and ask the teacher to sign off that you were there --&nbsp; be sure to include the name of the activity that you actually attended.&nbsp; Return the sheet to room 134 and you're done! </p><p> To keep from getting an absence:<b><br /></b></p><ul><li><b>Go to the activity that you chose -- and don't leave!</b></li><li>Make sure your teacher knows you are there.</li><li>DO NOT sign the bottom of a roster. These names are not included in attendance and will result in an absence. </li><li><b>Don't ask a <u>substitute</u> to 'call you in', they can't! Absences in activities with a substitute teacher cannot be cleared!</b><br /></li><li>If you forgot to sign up before the end of lunch, come to the 8th period office to get a pass</li><li>Turn in your pass to the sponsor as soon as you arrive! </li><li>QUESTIONS? See Mrs. Burch in the 8th period office (room 134)<br /></li></ul><p></p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
LOST AND FOUND list is FRIDAY!&nbsp; To be removed you must clear your 8th period absences BEFORE 4pm today. It's simple: click on the absence link from your home page, print the page and ask the teacher to sign off that you were there --&nbsp; be sure to include the name of the activity that you actually attended.&nbsp; Return the sheet to room 134 and you're done! To keep from getting an absence: Go to the activity that you chose -- and don't leave!Make sure your teacher knows you are there. DO NOT sign the bottom of a roster. These names are not included in attendance and will result in an absence. Don't ask a substitute to 'call you in', they can't! Absences in activities with a substitute teacher cannot be cleared! If you forgot to sign up before the end of lunch, come to the 8th period office to get a pass Turn in your pass to the sponsor as soon as you arrive! QUESTIONS? See Mrs. Burch in the 8th period office (room 134)
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2403</id>
		<title>Sochi Olympics and the NSF</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Are you a sports nut? Excited about the upcoming Winter Olympics in Sochi, Russia? <a href="http://www.nsf.gov/news/special_reports/winterolympics/index.jsp?WT.mc_id=USNSF_51">Check out the National Science Foundation's 10-part video collection</a> that delves into the physics, engineering, chemistry, design, and mathematics behind the world's foremost sporting event.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Are you a sports nut? Excited about the upcoming Winter Olympics in Sochi, Russia? Check out the National Science Foundation's 10-part video collection that delves into the physics, engineering, chemistry, design, and mathematics behind the world's foremost sporting event.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2402</id>
		<title>
Info Session on Camp Rising Sun, Friday, Jan. 17, B Block
</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>If you&#8217;re interested in a really amazing summer leadership experience, where you make life-long friends from around the world &#8211; and tuition is free-- come to the College and Career Center on Friday, Jan. 17, during B Block, to learn about Camp Rising Sun. This is a leadership camp in Upstate New York whose alumni include former UN officials, ambassadors and well-known writers and filmmakers. Hear from TJ classmates who went last year about how it has impacted their lives. </p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
If you&#8217;re interested in a really amazing summer leadership experience, where you make life-long friends from around the world &#8211; and tuition is free-- come to the College and Career Center on Friday, Jan. 17, during B Block, to learn about Camp Rising Sun. This is a leadership camp in Upstate New York whose alumni include former UN officials, ambassadors and well-known writers and filmmakers. Hear from TJ classmates who went last year about how it has impacted their lives.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2393</id>
		<title>Attention Science Fair Participants</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<b>For Nonsensitive Projects:</b><p>Please submit your nonsensitive science fair project forms to room 121 work by January 6. Remember, this is the first day of school after the winter break!</p><b>For Sensitive Projects:</b><p> Your paperwork has been reviewed by TJ&#8217;s Scientific Review Committee. Please find your sponsor ASAP for a list of necessary corrections, and see Dr. Burden in 141wk before winter break to discuss how to correct your submission. </p><p>For any other questions or concerns, please email Dr. Burden (dkburden@fcps.edu), or visit his office in room 141 wk.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
For Nonsensitive Projects: Please submit your nonsensitive science fair project forms to room 121 work by January 6. Remember, this is the first day of school after the winter break! For Sensitive Projects: Your paperwork has been reviewed by TJ&#8217;s Scientific Review Committee. Please find your sponsor ASAP for a list of necessary corrections, and see Dr. Burden in 141wk before winter break to discuss how to correct your submission. For any other questions or concerns, please email Dr. Burden (dkburden@fcps.edu), or visit his office in room 141 wk.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2385</id>
		<title>Churros for FPS</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p> Churros...Friday, December 13th, Future Problem Solving will be selling fresh churros in the J- Lounge during break for $1 each. Come out before they sell out and support them for the upcoming Qualifying Problem!</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Churros...Friday, December 13th, Future Problem Solving will be selling fresh churros in the J- Lounge during break for $1 each. Come out before they sell out and support them for the upcoming Qualifying Problem!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2380</id>
		<title>Solar Schools Initiative Petition</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p> Did you know that TJ has 22 solar panels on its roof? In order to expand clean energy use in the county's schools, TJ's Environmental Impact Club is petitioning the School Board to create a process for Parent-Teacher Associations to raise money for solar energy. <a href="http://www.change.org/petitions/start-a-solar-schools-initiative">Sign the petition here and help the environment!</a></p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Did you know that TJ has 22 solar panels on its roof? In order to expand clean energy use in the county's schools, TJ's Environmental Impact Club is petitioning the School Board to create a process for Parent-Teacher Associations to raise money for solar energy. Sign the petition here and help the environment!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2378</id>
		<title>
Computer Science Education Week Is Here  Lets Learn Something New
</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>In honor of the #HourOfCode movement that was launched this week for Computer Science Education Week 2013, we're going to be planning a few 8th period CS tutorials in January and February. We want YOU to decide what they're about! We're hoping this will be a nice jump start to the upcoming Hackathon that is also in the works for the spring. <a href="http://bit.ly/CSTutorials">Tell us what you are interested in here.</a></p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
In honor of the #HourOfCode movement that was launched this week for Computer Science Education Week 2013, we're going to be planning a few 8th period CS tutorials in January and February. We want YOU to decide what they're about! We're hoping this will be a nice jump start to the upcoming Hackathon that is also in the works for the spring. Tell us what you are interested in here.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2377</id>
		<title>Wednesday, December 11, will be an anchor day</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
If there is school on Wednesday, December 11, then the schedule will be modified to be an anchor day.&nbsp; Regardless of a school day on Wednesday, the schedule for Thursday and Friday will remain the same as block days.
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
If there is school on Wednesday, December 11, then the schedule will be modified to be an anchor day.&nbsp; Regardless of a school day on Wednesday, the schedule for Thursday and Friday will remain the same as block days.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2368</id>
		<title>Submit to Threshold!</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Do YOU want to be published? We want your prose, poetry, photos, music, and art to be featured in Threshold, TJ's Literary Magazine! </p><p>Did you know TJ also has its own writing contest? Submit prose or poetry to the theme of "Cipher" to the Shadwell writing contest! Submissions will be sent for judging to authors around the country, and the winning pieces will be featured in a special section of the Threshold magazine!</p><p>Pick up a submission form for both Threshold and Shadwell from a folder around the school or your English classroom and drop them off to the box outside Room 107 or <a href="mailto:thresholdlitmag@gmail.com">email submissions to thresholdlitmag@gmail.com</a>.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Do YOU want to be published? We want your prose, poetry, photos, music, and art to be featured in Threshold, TJ's Literary Magazine! Did you know TJ also has its own writing contest? Submit prose or poetry to the theme of "Cipher" to the Shadwell writing contest! Submissions will be sent for judging to authors around the country, and the winning pieces will be featured in a special section of the Threshold magazine! Pick up a submission form for both Threshold and Shadwell from a folder around the school or your English classroom and drop them off to the box outside Room 107 or email submissions to thresholdlitmag@gmail.com.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2366</id>
		<title>Poetry Out Loud Finalists</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Please extend the deepest congratulations to the following students for making it to the TJ Poetry Out Loud Finals:<br /> Zara Batalvi - Faith Ellen Lam - Clarissa Scoggins - Ian Car - Cedric Bernard - Bailey Knight - Maya Omais - Nila Selvaraj - Dylan Seng - Nur Simsek - Jose Acuna - Mathew Alexander - Aldrayne Cabansag - Pegah Moradi - Hannah Pho - Lucia Tian - Iris Hyon - Nan Baker - Sara Mueller</p><p> Finalists, please make sure you have two poems prepared and two copies of each of your poems for the judges! Good luck. </p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Please extend the deepest congratulations to the following students for making it to the TJ Poetry Out Loud Finals: Zara Batalvi - Faith Ellen Lam - Clarissa Scoggins - Ian Car - Cedric Bernard - Bailey Knight - Maya Omais - Nila Selvaraj - Dylan Seng - Nur Simsek - Jose Acuna - Mathew Alexander - Aldrayne Cabansag - Pegah Moradi - Hannah Pho - Lucia Tian - Iris Hyon - Nan Baker - Sara Mueller Finalists, please make sure you have two poems prepared and two copies of each of your poems for the judges! Good luck.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2356</id>
		<title>Military Academy Visits Monday</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Interested in applying to West Point or Annapolis, or just curious to know what it&#8217;s like to go there? At lunchtime, the College and Career Center is hosting a current West Point cadet, Molly Shannon and, during 8th Period, current Annapolis cadet Josh Chester. These students can answer your questions on applying to a service academy and living in a structured, military environment. Sophomores and Juniors considering applying to one of the service academies are particularly encouraged to attend. Be sure to remember to sign up for the Annapolis session during 8th Period.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Interested in applying to West Point or Annapolis, or just curious to know what it&#8217;s like to go there? At lunchtime, the College and Career Center is hosting a current West Point cadet, Molly Shannon and, during 8th Period, current Annapolis cadet Josh Chester. These students can answer your questions on applying to a service academy and living in a structured, military environment. Sophomores and Juniors considering applying to one of the service academies are particularly encouraged to attend. Be sure to remember to sign up for the Annapolis session during 8th Period.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2352</id>
		<title>F=ma Physics Competition</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>To register for the F=ma physics competition, bring an envelope with $5, your Name, and your Email Address by Tuesday, November 26th! Hand the envelope to one of the physics team officers (Ivy Ren, Archis Bhandarkar, Shankar Balasubramanian, Arun Kannan, or Ray Liu), preferably during physics team Friday B Block. There will be no exceptions to the deadline, and we will not accept your registration if it doesn't have all of the pertaining components. Details on the competition can be found at <a href="http://activities.tjhsst.edu/physics/">our website</a> or <a href="http://aapt.org/physicsteam/2013/">AAPT</a>.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
To register for the F=ma physics competition, bring an envelope with $5, your Name, and your Email Address by Tuesday, November 26th! Hand the envelope to one of the physics team officers (Ivy Ren, Archis Bhandarkar, Shankar Balasubramanian, Arun Kannan, or Ray Liu), preferably during physics team Friday B Block. There will be no exceptions to the deadline, and we will not accept your registration if it doesn't have all of the pertaining components. Details on the competition can be found at our website or AAPT.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2351</id>
		<title>Jefferson Collaborative Inquiry Network</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Want to help shape the future of TJ? Please take 3 minutes to respond to <a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1AQAsuCR50ofcwgSBM3_0ifpR0BfAQizIckyGwk1wJ4s/viewform">this survey on the Jefferson Collaborative Inquiry Network</a> and keep TJ at the forefront of innovation. Thanks.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Want to help shape the future of TJ? Please take 3 minutes to respond to this survey on the Jefferson Collaborative Inquiry Network and keep TJ at the forefront of innovation. Thanks.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2345</id>
		<title>TJ3Sat - Historys First High School Satellite</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p> After 7 years of work, TJ3Sat is finally launching! The launch window opens at 7:30pm on Tuesday, November 19th out of Wallops Flight Facility and will be the first high school built satellite in history. To find out more about TJ3Sat, how you can view the launch, and how you can help TJ make history, come to the TJ3Sat info session Monday 11/18 during 8th period. </p><p>For more information, visit <a href="http://www.tjhsst.edu/students/activities/tj3sat/">the TJ3Sat info page</a>.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
After 7 years of work, TJ3Sat is finally launching! The launch window opens at 7:30pm on Tuesday, November 19th out of Wallops Flight Facility and will be the first high school built satellite in history. To find out more about TJ3Sat, how you can view the launch, and how you can help TJ make history, come to the TJ3Sat info session Monday 11/18 during 8th period. For more information, visit the TJ3Sat info page.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2330</id>
		<title>TJ Writing Center</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>The TJ Writing Center is now open during JLC in Trailer 35. Stop by in order to work with a tutor in order to receive feedback on your writing!</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
The TJ Writing Center is now open during JLC in Trailer 35. Stop by in order to work with a tutor in order to receive feedback on your writing!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2327</id>
		<title>Update: UVA November 4 Trip Cancelled</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p><b>Update</b>: Unfortunately, the UVA trip planned for the Teacher Work Day on Monday will need to be re-scheduled because we did not get enough students to participate. We will reschedule this trip for the spring, so please watch announcements from the College and Career Center. I encourage all of you who can get transportation down to Charlottesville on Monday to attend the STEM and Architecture Day event that you registered for &#8211; it should be great! Please see Mrs. Kropf to pick up your checks.</p><p>For juniors and seniors who would like to visit UVA or William and Mary on the Nov. 4 teacher work day, Scholars Travel is operating two tours that will leave the TJ parking lot early Monday morning and return early evening. The cost for each trip is $59. The William and Mary bus will leave TJ at 7:00, and a bus for participants in UVA&#8217;s STEM and Architecture Program will leave TJ at 7:30 am. <b>Students must register online for the UVA program.</b> Students must sign up for each trip in the College and Career Center. See your email from Mrs. Kropf or stop by the College and Career Center for more information.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Update: Unfortunately, the UVA trip planned for the Teacher Work Day on Monday will need to be re-scheduled because we did not get enough students to participate. We will reschedule this trip for the spring, so please watch announcements from the College and Career Center. I encourage all of you who can get transportation down to Charlottesville on Monday to attend the STEM and Architecture Day event that you registered for &#8211; it should be great! Please see Mrs. Kropf to pick up your checks. For juniors and seniors who would like to visit UVA or William and Mary on the Nov. 4 teacher work day, Scholars Travel is operating two tours that will leave the TJ parking lot early Monday morning and return early evening. The cost for each trip is $59. The William and Mary bus will leave TJ at 7:00, and a bus for participants in UVA&#8217;s STEM and Architecture Program will leave TJ at 7:30 am. Students must register online for the UVA program. Students must sign up for each trip in the College and Career Center. See your email from Mrs. Kropf or stop by the College and Career Center for more information.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2323</id>
		<title>TJ Runway</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Come to TJ Runway this Wednesday B block and discover the role of technology (namely 3D printing) in the fashion industry and its influence on the beginning of a fashion revolution. After a brief presentation, we will be watching an Iris Van Herpen Haute Couture Fashion Show. Iris Van Herpen is a Dutch designer, and is one of the first to experiment with and incorporate 3D printing into her fashion, and to have an entire fashion show featuring only 3D printed garments. Also, in celebration of Halloween, there will be candy. Our design competition will also continue as usual! Please email any questions to <a href="mailto:tj.runway.14@gmail.com">tj.runway.14@gmail.com</a>. Hope to see you there!</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Come to TJ Runway this Wednesday B block and discover the role of technology (namely 3D printing) in the fashion industry and its influence on the beginning of a fashion revolution. After a brief presentation, we will be watching an Iris Van Herpen Haute Couture Fashion Show. Iris Van Herpen is a Dutch designer, and is one of the first to experiment with and incorporate 3D printing into her fashion, and to have an entire fashion show featuring only 3D printed garments. Also, in celebration of Halloween, there will be candy. Our design competition will also continue as usual! Please email any questions to tj.runway.14@gmail.com. Hope to see you there!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2311</id>
		<title>Seniors vs. Juniors Powderpuff Information</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p> All participants must: </p><ul><li>submit an <a href="http://colonialathletics.org/library/files/ColonialAthletics_org/files/Emergency%20Care%20Information%20form.pdf ">Emergency Care Card</a></li><li>submit a T-shirt form including a 15-letter maximum nickname and $20 (cash or check made out to TJHSST)</li><li>have a Physical on file. </li></ul><p></p><p> All forms are due on November 6, 2013 to Room 151. There will be NO EXCEPTIONS since practices will begin promptly after forms are due. Practices will be held during A Blocks on the Softball field. A tentative practice schedule will be released soon. Students interested in coaching and/or cheerleading should email <a href="mailto:tjclassof2014@gmail.com">tjclassof2014@gmail.com</a>. </p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
All participants must: submit an Emergency Care Card submit a T-shirt form including a 15-letter maximum nickname and $20 (cash or check made out to TJHSST) have a Physical on file. All forms are due on November 6, 2013 to Room 151. There will be NO EXCEPTIONS since practices will begin promptly after forms are due. Practices will be held during A Blocks on the Softball field. A tentative practice schedule will be released soon. Students interested in coaching and/or cheerleading should email tjclassof2014@gmail.com.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2309</id>
		<title>TJ Runway</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Hello art, fashion, and tech enthusiasts! Looking for a fun outlet to express your creativity? Love art, fashion, and technology? Come to TJ Runway Wednesdays B blocks and be a designer, model, or help out with the business/technological aspects of our end-of-the-year runway showcase, no past experience necessary. Along with our yearlong design challenge, we will be conducting weekly design challenges as well complete with prizes.</p><p>Add our calendar by entering <input value="sedkr6msq7jgao9idg7m9mkid4@group.calendar.google.com" style="background:transparent;border:0;font-size:12px;width:340px" onclick="select()"> into the 'Add Calendars' tab on Google Calendar to keep track of each weekly challenge so you can decide which ones interest you. Feel free to email any questions directly to <a href="mailto:tj.runway.14@gmail.com">tj.runway.14@gmail.com</a>. Hope to see you there, and there will be food.</p><p></p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Hello art, fashion, and tech enthusiasts! Looking for a fun outlet to express your creativity? Love art, fashion, and technology? Come to TJ Runway Wednesdays B blocks and be a designer, model, or help out with the business/technological aspects of our end-of-the-year runway showcase, no past experience necessary. Along with our yearlong design challenge, we will be conducting weekly design challenges as well complete with prizes. Add our calendar by entering into the 'Add Calendars' tab on Google Calendar to keep track of each weekly challenge so you can decide which ones interest you. Feel free to email any questions directly to tj.runway.14@gmail.com. Hope to see you there, and there will be food.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2298</id>
		<title>Improving TJ</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Dear Students,</p><p>Based on your feedback and thoughtful ideas regarding ways in which to improve the TJ environment, the following items have been approved by the administration for change:</p><p>Interior Design: The Mural Club has been invited to participate in generating ideas on how
]]>
			<![CDATA[
to best enhance the building. All students are invited to become involved in making the school a more beautiful place.</p> Teachers are also encouraged to hang their students work throughout the building. <p>Outdoor classes: Many teachers take advantage of this as their lessons and the weather permits. However, we will communicate to all teachers that this opportunity exists and invite them to use this option.</p><p>Applauding student effort: Post cards, designed by the Arts Honor Society, will be distributed to teachers so that they can mail them home to recognize students' outstanding individual effort in all areas including character, academics, athletics, and leadership. If, however, if you are interested in submitting a design for the card please contact Mr. DeRose by November 1. </p><p>One Question Grant: You are all invited to submit a One Question Grant Proposal. Please go to the TJ Website, click on "Student Life", then click on One Question Grant, then download the One Question Grant Application.</p><p>Sincerely, Mrs. Lewis</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Dear Students, Based on your feedback and thoughtful ideas regarding ways in which to improve the TJ environment, the following items have been approved by the administration for change: Interior Design: The Mural Club has been invited to participate in generating ideas on how to best enhance the building. All students are invited to become involved in making the school a more beautiful place. Teachers are also encouraged to hang their students work throughout the building. Outdoor classes: Many teachers take advantage of this as their lessons and the weather permits. However, we will communicate to all teachers that this opportunity exists and invite them to use this option. Applauding student effort: Post cards, designed by the Arts Honor Society, will be distributed to teachers so that they can mail them home to recognize students' outstanding individual effort in all areas including character, academics, athletics, and leadership. If, however, if you are interested in submitting a design for the card please contact Mr. DeRose by November 1. One Question Grant: You are all invited to submit a One Question Grant Proposal. Please go to the TJ Website, click on "Student Life", then click on One Question Grant, then download the One Question Grant Application. Sincerely, Mrs. Lewis
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2261</id>
		<title>TJ Runway Club</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p> Modeled after the hit Emmy nominated TV show "Project Runway", TJ Runway is the perfect club for any fashion enthusiast. Love design? You can learn to design and create clothing just like your favorite designers and brands; you can even compete in a competition similar to the TV show Project Runway. Love photography? You can create and edit a fashion photography portfolio to be showcased at our fashion show at the end of the year. Love being a leader? You could join this club to develop leadership and planning experience. Interested in modeling? TJ Runway will most definitely need models for the end of the year fashion showcase. Or maybe you could just use this activity as creative time-- a break from the normal school day. Whatever the reason, TJ Runway is a welcoming environment for beginner and advanced designers alike. All you need to do is bring your enthusiasm for creativity and your personal sense of fashion. </p><p> The interest meeting is this Wednesday the 25th during B-block. Come with your friends to learn more about the club and enjoy some great food! We hope to see you there, and if you have any questions, please feel free to email us at <a href="mailto:tj.runway.2011@gmail.com">tj.runway.2011@gmail.com</a>.</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Modeled after the hit Emmy nominated TV show "Project Runway", TJ Runway is the perfect club for any fashion enthusiast. Love design? You can learn to design and create clothing just like your favorite designers and brands; you can even compete in a competition similar to the TV show Project Runway. Love photography? You can create and edit a fashion photography portfolio to be showcased at our fashion show at the end of the year. Love being a leader? You could join this club to develop leadership and planning experience. Interested in modeling? TJ Runway will most definitely need models for the end of the year fashion showcase. Or maybe you could just use this activity as creative time-- a break from the normal school day. Whatever the reason, TJ Runway is a welcoming environment for beginner and advanced designers alike. All you need to do is bring your enthusiasm for creativity and your personal sense of fashion. The interest meeting is this Wednesday the 25th during B-block. Come with your friends to learn more about the club and enjoy some great food! We hope to see you there, and if you have any questions, please feel free to email us at tj.runway.2011@gmail.com.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2225</id>
		<title>Academic Advocacy Guidelines</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
Whenever you face difficult academic conflicts, sometimes you can use some advocacy techniques to help yourself out.&nbsp; The following recommendations have been devised by the TJ leadership team:<br /><br /><a href="http://www.tjhsst.edu/~emglazer/studentadvocacy.pdf">http://www.tjhsst.edu/~emglazer/studentadvocacy.pdf</a><br /><br />The key is to be proactive with good time management skills!&nbsp; Also, make sure you turn to your counselor for additional advice.<br />
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Whenever you face difficult academic conflicts, sometimes you can use some advocacy techniques to help yourself out.&nbsp; The following recommendations have been devised by the TJ leadership team:http://www.tjhsst.edu/~emglazer/studentadvocacy.pdfThe key is to be proactive with good time management skills!&nbsp; Also, make sure you turn to your counselor for additional advice.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2223</id>
		<title>Siemens Competition</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<div><div>Greetings Juniors &nbsp;- IF you completed a TEAM summer research project AND are considering to apply to the Siemens Competition, please send an email message to Dr. Kennedy with the following information:</div><div><br /></div><div>TO: brian.kennedy@fcps.edu</div><div>SUBJECT: Siemens Competition &#8211; Your Names&nbsp;</div><div>Message:</div><div>Your Name:&nbsp;</div><div>Project Title (draft):</div><div>Note, enter multiple names for group projects. &nbsp;More information forthcoming to those who respond. &nbsp;Note that for the Siemens Competition, Junior&#8217;s MUST enter as a TEAM.</div></div>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Greetings Juniors &nbsp;- IF you completed a TEAM summer research project AND are considering to apply to the Siemens Competition, please send an email message to Dr. Kennedy with the following information:TO: brian.kennedy@fcps.eduSUBJECT: Siemens Competition &#8211; Your Names&nbsp;Message:Your Name:&nbsp;Project Title (draft):Note, enter multiple names for group projects. &nbsp;More information forthcoming to those who respond. &nbsp;Note that for the Siemens Competition, Junior&#8217;s MUST enter as a TEAM.
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2219</id>
		<title>Summer Assignments</title>
		<text>
		<![CDATA[

		
		<!--[if gte mso 9]>
		<xml>
			<w:WordDocument>
				<w:View>Normal</w:View>
				<w:Zoom>0</w:Zoom>
				<w:TrackMoves/>
				<w:TrackFormatting/>
				<w:PunctuationKerning/>
				<w:ValidateAgainstSchemas/>
				<w:SaveIfXMLInvalid>false</w:SaveIfXMLInvalid>
				<w:IgnoreMixedContent>false</w:IgnoreMixedContent>
				<w:AlwaysShowPlaceholderText>false</w:AlwaysShowPlaceholderText>
				<w:DoNotPromoteQF/>
				<w:LidThemeOther>EN-US</w:LidThemeOther>
				<w:LidThemeAsian>X-NONE</w:LidThemeAsian>
				<w:LidThemeComplexScript>X-NONE</w:LidThemeComplexScript>
				<w:Compatibility>
					<w:BreakWrappedTables/>
					<w:SnapToGridInCell/>
					<w:WrapTextWithPunct/>
					<w:UseAsianBreakRules/>
					<w:DontGrowAutofit/>
					<w:SplitPgBreakAndParaMark/>
					<w:DontVertAlignCellWithSp/>
					<w:DontBreakConstrainedForcedTables/>
					<w:DontVertAlignInTxbx/>
					<w:Word11KerningPairs/>
					<w:CachedColBalance/>
				</w:Compatibility>
				<w:BrowserLevel>MicrosoftInternetExplorer4</w:BrowserLevel>
				<m:mathPr>
					<m:mathFont m:val='Cambria Math'/>
					<m:brkBin m:val='before'/>
					<m:brkBinSub m:val='&#45;-'/>
					<m:smallFrac m:val='off'/>
					<m:dispDef/>
					<m:lMargin m:val='0'/>
					<m:rMargin m:val='0'/>
					<m:defJc m:val='centerGroup'/>
					<m:wrapIndent m:val='1440'/>
					<m:intLim m:val='subSup'/>
					<m:naryLim m:val='undOvr'/>
				</m:mathPr>
			</w:WordDocument>
		</xml>
		<![endif]-->
		<p>
			<span style="font-size:10.0pt;font-family:" arial','sans-serif';color:black'="">Congratulations on another great </span>
			<span style="font-size:10.0pt;font-family:" arial','sans-serif''="">school year! As we prepare for the next school year, please make sure you refer to the following website for assignments that should be completed prior to the start of next school year: </span>
		</p>
		<p>
			<span style="font-size:10.0pt;font-family:" arial','sans-serif''="">
				<a href="http://www.tjhsst.edu/summer-assignments.php">http://www.tjhsst.edu/summer-assignments.php</a>&nbsp;
				
				<br />
				<br /> One assignment for all students is to read the book, &#8220;
				
				<a href="http://www.amazon.com/Drive-Surprising-Truth-About-Motivates/dp/1594484805/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1371214923&amp;sr=8-1&amp;keywords=drive+the+surprising+truth+about+what+motivates+us" target="_blank">
					<em>
						<span style="font-family:" arial','sans-serif';color:windowtext;="" ;font-style:normal'="">Drive: The surprising Truth About What Motivates</span>
					</em>
					<span class="apple-converted-space">
						<i>
							<span style="text-decoration:none;text-underline:none">&nbsp;</span>
						</i>
					</span>
					<span style="color: windowtext; background-position: initial initial; background-repeat: initial initial;">Us&#8221; by Daniel H. Pink</span>
				</a>
				<span class="apple-converted-space">
					<span style="background-position: initial initial; background-repeat: initial initial;"> to begin thinking about the 2013-2014 One Question selected by the TJ students and teachers, &#8220;How can we maintain a passion for learning in a school system where a pronounced emphasis on achieving good grades has a tendency to reduce genuine interest</span>
				</span>
			</span>
			<span class="apple-converted-space">
				<span style="font-size:10.0pt;font-family: " arial','sans-serif';background:white'=""> in gaining a deeper understanding of subject material?&#8221;</span>
			</span>
		</p>
		<p>
			<span style="font-size:10.0pt;font-family:" arial','sans-serif''="">Contact information for each assignment is posted to the website.&nbsp; </span></p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Congratulations on another great school year! As we prepare for the next school year, please make sure you refer to the following website for assignments that should be completed prior to the start of next school year: http://www.tjhsst.edu/summer-assignments.php&nbsp; One assignment for all students is to read the book, &#8220;Drive: The surprising Truth About What Motivates&nbsp;Us&#8221; by Daniel H. Pink to begin thinking about the 2013-2014 One Question selected by the TJ students and teachers, &#8220;How can we maintain a passion for learning in a school system where a pronounced emphasis on achieving good grades has a tendency to reduce genuine interest in gaining a deeper understanding of subject material?&#8221; Contact information for each assignment is posted to the website.&nbsp;
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2212</id>
		<title>Smart Grid Info</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Do you want to learn how Smart Grids work? Are you interested in improving America's energy security? Then visit <a href="http://smartgridforamerica.com/">Smart Grid for America</a> and sign our petition to get Congress to support our cause!</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Do you want to learn how Smart Grids work? Are you interested in improving America's energy security? Then visit Smart Grid for America and sign our petition to get Congress to support our cause!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2211</id>
		<title>Ways to Improve Study Habits</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Do you want to know how to improve your study habits and possible achieve more personal academic success? Or do you want to open your mind to skills that may serve you well in the future?</p><p><a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8JnxUtqW-NE&amp;feature=youtu.be" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Watch this video</a><wbr>, created as part of the One Question class, to learn about effective study strategies. Afterwards, please fill out <a href="http://www.surveymonkey.com/s/CPTLKY7" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">this survey</a>&nbsp;for us to receive feedback. Thanks!</p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Do you want to know how to improve your study habits and possible achieve more personal academic success? Or do you want to open your mind to skills that may serve you well in the future?Watch this video, created as part of the One Question class, to learn about effective study strategies. Afterwards, please fill out this survey&nbsp;for us to receive feedback. Thanks!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2207</id>
		<title>TJ Dreams</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<p>Thank You for all your support and contributions to TJ Dreams! We have posted responses all around the school. Please take a few seconds to respond to the Google Forms survey as well. Thank You again!</p><p><a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1SM2LjzbxQxsffMczGXc9eQEMnSHDONjpyde7xa4F4go/viewform" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">View survey</a></p>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Thank You for all your support and contributions to TJ Dreams! We have posted responses all around the school. Please take a few seconds to respond to the Google Forms survey as well. Thank You again!View survey
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<post>
		<id>2041</id>
		<title>tjTODAY Online Newspaper</title>
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
<span style="color: rgb(2, 2, 2); font-size: 13px; ">Hey Jefferson!&nbsp;Want to know about the current happenings at our school? Head on over to our&nbsp;</span><a href="http://www.tjhsst.edu/studentlife/publications/tjtoday/wordpress/" style="font-family: 'Open Sans', Arial, Helvetica, Roboto, 'Droid Sans', sans-serif; ">online newspaper</a><span style="color: rgb(2, 2, 2); font-size: 13px; ">&nbsp;to read more about recent sorts events, student plays, eighth period clubs and more. And while you&#8217;re at it, make sure to like our&nbsp;</span><a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/TjTODAY/162791193759064" style="font-family: 'Open Sans', Arial, Helvetica, Roboto, 'Droid Sans', sans-serif; ">Facebook page</a><span style="color: rgb(2, 2, 2); font-size: 13px; ">&nbsp;and follow us on Twitter at&nbsp;</span><a href="http://twitter.com/tjtoday_news" style="font-family: 'Open Sans', Arial, Helvetica, Roboto, 'Droid Sans', sans-serif; ">@tjtoday_news</a><span style="color: rgb(2, 2, 2); font-size: 13px; ">!</span>
]]>
		</text>
		<text_strip>
			<![CDATA[
Hey Jefferson!&nbsp;Want to know about the current happenings at our school? Head on over to our&nbsp;online newspaper&nbsp;to read more about recent sorts events, student plays, eighth period clubs and more. And while you&#8217;re at it, make sure to like our&nbsp;Facebook page&nbsp;and follow us on Twitter at&nbsp;@tjtoday_news!
]]>
		</text_strip>
	</post>
	<error/>
	<debug/>
</news>